{"id": 4026, "data": "The veteran big man amassed an all-time team record 30 rebounds in the Blazers’ 118-103 win over Detroit on Saturday, besting the previous mark of 27 rebounds set by Sidney Wicks in 1975.", "label": [[52, 54, "CARDINAL"], [147, 149, "CARDINAL"], [166, 178, "PERSON"], [182, 186, "DATE"], [97, 104, "GPE"], [108, 116, "DATE"], [80, 87, "SCORE"], [67, 78, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4032, "data": "The others were Dwight Howard with the Charlotte Hornets in 2018 and Kevin Love with the Minnesota Timberwolves in 2010.", "label": [[16, 29, "PERSON"], [39, 56, "ORG"], [69, 79, "PERSON"], [89, 111, "ORG"], [115, 119, "DATE"], [60, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4038, "data": "Saturday’s victory pulled the Blazers to within 1.5 games of the fifth-place Los Angeles Lakers.", "label": [[0, 8, "DATE"], [30, 37, "ORG"], [77, 95, "ORG"], [48, 51, "CARDINAL"], [65, 76, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4044, "data": "With the Warriors shooting upcourt, Wiseman took a pass in stride on the right wing and went up for a layup.", "label": [[36, 43, "PERSON"], [5, 17, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4050, "data": "He quickly rose, but was limping and wincing, which led to a Warriors timeout as Wiseman headed to the locker room.", "label": [[61, 69, "PERSON"], [81, 88, "PERSON"], [103, 114, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4056, "data": "Snell left Friday night’s 120-108 win over Chicago in the third quarter with the injury and did not return.", "label": [[26, 33, "SCORE"], [11, 17, "DATE"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [43, 50, "GPE"], [54, 71, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 4062, "data": "Snell’s status will be updated following the team’s return to Atlanta.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [62, 69, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4074, "data": "A native of Montreal, Quebec, Birch is averaging 4.7 points, 4.4 rebounds and 16.5 minutes in 188 career games (30 starts) during four seasons in Orlando (2017-21).", "label": [[12, 20, "GPE"], [22, 28, "GPE"], [30, 35, "PERSON"], [49, 52, "CARDINAL"], [61, 64, "CARDINAL"], [94, 97, "CARDINAL"], [130, 142, "DATE"], [146, 153, "GPE"], [155, 162, "DATE"], [112, 114, "CARDINAL"], [78, 90, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 4080, "data": "On the international stage, Birch represented Canada at the 2019 FIBA World Cup in China.", "label": [[28, 33, "PERSON"], [46, 52, "GPE"], [56, 79, "ORG"], [83, 88, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4086, "data": "NASHVILLE, Tenn. (AP) — Vanderbilt guard Scotty Pippen Jr. has declared for the NBA draft without signing with an agent to keep his options open.", "label": [[24, 34, "GPE"], [41, 58, "PERSON"], [0, 9, "GPE"], [76, 89, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4092, "data": "“We all have dreams and I am ready to pursue mine,” Pippen said.", "label": [[52, 58, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4098, "data": "Coach Jerry Stackhouse said Pippen earned the right to check out his draft status and has Vanderbilt’s full support.", "label": [[6, 22, "PERSON"], [90, 100, "GPE"], [28, 34, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4104, "data": "Deandre Ayton (PHO) $7,900: Many people consider Ayton a bust but let’s slow down a bit.", "label": [[20, 26, "MONEY"], [49, 54, "PERSON"], [0, 13, "PERSON"], [15, 18, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4110, "data": "We love that against a Wizards team that ranks last in points allowed while playing at the fastest pace in the league.", "label": [[23, 30, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4116, "data": "Brooklyn is not a scary matchup either, sitting 25th in defensive efficiency.", "label": [[48, 52, "ORDINAL"], [0, 8, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4128, "data": "That shouldn’t be hard to duplicate against a Cleveland team with a bottom-five defense since the opening month.", "label": [[46, 55, "ORG"], [94, 111, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4134, "data": "In the 18 games that Joel has missed this season, Howard is averaging nearly 30 FD points per game.", "label": [[7, 9, "CARDINAL"], [21, 25, "PERSON"], [50, 56, "PERSON"], [77, 79, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4140, "data": "The Thunder are currently without Shai Gilgeous-Alexander, Al Horford, Darius Bazley and Isaiah Roby, leaving Kenrich to feast.", "label": [[4, 11, "ORG"], [34, 57, "PERSON"], [59, 69, "PERSON"], [71, 84, "PERSON"], [89, 100, "PERSON"], [110, 117, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4152, "data": "While he was limited in his first game with the Lakers, Drum played 27 minutes and provided one of his patented double-doubles on Thursday.", "label": [[48, 54, "ORG"], [130, 138, "DATE"], [56, 60, "PERSON"], [68, 78, "TIME"], [28, 33, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4158, "data": "The 20-year-old has started nine straight games and is playing nearly 26 minutes a night in that stretch.", "label": [[28, 32, "CARDINAL"], [70, 88, "TIME"], [4, 15, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4164, "data": "He has actually started for Mason Plumlee twice this week, combining for 77 FD points in those two outings.", "label": [[73, 75, "CARDINAL"], [95, 98, "CARDINAL"], [48, 57, "DATE"], [28, 41, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4170, "data": "ET, ABC • The Nets won the first meeting of the season with the Lakers, 109-98 on Feb. 18 , behind James Harden’s 23 points and 11 assists, Joe Harris’ 21 points and 6-for-7 shooting on 3-pointers, and 16 points from Kyrie Irving.", "label": [[10, 18, "ORG"], [27, 32, "ORDINAL"], [4, 7, "ORG"], [72, 78, "SCORE"], [82, 89, "DATE"], [99, 111, "PERSON"], [140, 150, "PERSON"], [152, 154, "CARDINAL"], [202, 204, "CARDINAL"], [217, 229, "PERSON"], [64, 70, "ORG"], [186, 196, "PRODUCT"], [166, 173, "CARDINAL"], [114, 116, "CARDINAL"], [128, 130, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4176, "data": "• This is a meeting of the team with the top-ranked offense (Brooklyn at 117.5) against the team with the top-ranked defense (Los Angeles at 105.6 allowed).", "label": [[61, 69, "GPE"], [73, 78, "CARDINAL"], [126, 137, "GPE"], [141, 146, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4182, "data": "They are led by Harris, who ranks third in the league in 3-point accuracy (48.4%) and sixth in total 3-pointers made (166) so far this season.", "label": [[16, 22, "PERSON"], [34, 39, "ORDINAL"], [75, 80, "PERCENT"], [86, 91, "ORDINAL"], [118, 121, "CARDINAL"], [101, 111, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4184, "data": "The Nets are 13-3 this season when Harris makes more than three 3-pointers, which he did in the first meeting with the Lakers.", "label": [[64, 74, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4188, "data": "Kyrie is shooting 52.0% from the field, 36.8% from 3-point range and 95% at the free throw line over 11 games in which the Nets have gone 9-2.", "label": [[138, 141, "SCORE"], [101, 103, "CARDINAL"], [40, 45, "PERCENT"], [69, 72, "PERCENT"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [18, 23, "PERCENT"], [119, 127, "ORG"], [51, 58, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4194, "data": "In 207 minutes with the trio of Harrell, Schroder and Kuzma on court, while LeBron and Davis are off court, the Lakers have a 107.4 offensive rating and 100.7 defensive rating and have outscored opponents by a total of 37 points.", "label": [[3, 14, "TIME"], [32, 39, "GPE"], [41, 49, "PERSON"], [54, 59, "PERSON"], [76, 82, "PERSON"], [87, 92, "PERSON"], [112, 118, "ORG"], [126, 131, "CARDINAL"], [153, 158, "CARDINAL"], [219, 221, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4200, "data": "The performance included an incredible stretch of 25 straight points in the second quarter by the Bulls guard.", "label": [[50, 52, "CARDINAL"], [98, 103, "ORG"], [72, 90, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4206, "data": "The 26-year-old has reached a new level of offensive efficiency in his fourth season with the Chicago Bulls, averaging 27.1 points on 50.7% shooting and 41.5% from deep.", "label": [[4, 15, "DATE"], [71, 77, "ORDINAL"], [94, 107, "ORG"], [119, 123, "CARDINAL"], [134, 139, "PERCENT"], [153, 158, "PERCENT"]]}
{"id": 4212, "data": "How will this affect the Clippers?", "label": [[25, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4218, "data": "There is not timetable for his return, and he will be re-evaluated in three to four weeks.", "label": [[70, 89, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4220, "data": "Now in his fourth season with the Clippers, Beverley is averaging 8.0 points while shooting 41.6% from 3-point range.", "label": [[103, 110, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4224, "data": "MILWAUKEE (AP) — The Milwaukee Bucks were without all five of their usual starters Friday night as they hosted the Charlotte Hornets a night after losing at Dallas.", "label": [[21, 36, "ORG"], [0, 9, "GPE"], [115, 132, "ORG"], [157, 163, "GPE"], [83, 89, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4230, "data": "Reigning two-time MVP Giannis Antetokounmpo missed a fourth straight game with a sore left knee that has kept him out of six of the Bucks’ last 11 contests.", "label": [[9, 12, "CARDINAL"], [18, 21, "PRODUCT"], [22, 43, "PERSON"], [132, 137, "ORG"], [121, 124, "CARDINAL"], [53, 59, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4236, "data": "“We didn’t know until like before the game, probably like 45 minutes before the game or something like that,” McDaniels said.", "label": [[58, 68, "TIME"], [110, 119, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4242, "data": "DiVincenzo, Holiday, Lopez and Middleton all had played Thursday.", "label": [[12, 19, "PERSON"], [21, 26, "PERSON"], [31, 40, "PERSON"], [0, 10, "PERSON"], [56, 64, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4254, "data": "These guys are a little banged up.” Charlotte also wasn’t close to full strength.", "label": [[36, 45, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4260, "data": "Malik Monk has been out the last week with a sprained right ankle.", "label": [[0, 10, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4262, "data": "“We always say it doesn’t matter who’s on the floor,” said Graham, who shot 6 of 12 from 3-point range.", "label": [[89, 96, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4266, "data": "Jeff Teague scored 19 and Bryn Forbes added 18 for the Bucks, who had seven players in double figures.", "label": [[0, 11, "PERSON"], [19, 21, "CARDINAL"], [26, 37, "PERSON"], [44, 46, "CARDINAL"], [55, 60, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4272, "data": "Hobbled since then with a nagging foot injury, the 40-year-old center decided to come back home in hopes of reviving his career in a second stint with Barcelona.", "label": [[51, 62, "DATE"], [133, 139, "ORDINAL"], [151, 160, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4278, "data": "Bayern won 82-72.", "label": [[11, 16, "SCORE"], [0, 6, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4284, "data": "The two-time All-Star is dealing with a right knee injury, which he sustained on Thursday against the Los Angeles Lakers, and will be further reevaluated.", "label": [[13, 21, "PRODUCT"], [81, 89, "DATE"], [98, 120, "ORG"], [4, 7, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4290, "data": "Oladipo had 18 points, four rebounds and three steals in 25 minutes before exiting with under six minutes left in the game, which the Heat won 110-104 .", "label": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [12, 14, "CARDINAL"], [23, 27, "CARDINAL"], [41, 46, "CARDINAL"], [57, 67, "TIME"], [94, 105, "TIME"], [143, 150, "SCORE"], [134, 138, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4296, "data": "DiVincenzo has surpassed 29+ minutes in each of his last five games and he’s hit 5x value at his current price the past three games in which Antetokounmpo has been sidelined.", "label": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 36, "TIME"], [52, 61, "ORDINAL"], [141, 154, "PERSON"], [81, 83, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4302, "data": "The Charlotte Hornets have given up a league-worst 48.97 FD points per game to power forwards, which bodes well for Portis if Antetokounmpo is indeed ruled out.", "label": [[4, 21, "ORG"], [51, 56, "CARDINAL"], [126, 139, "PERSON"], [116, 122, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4308, "data": "After going with Chris Boucher on Thursday – who exploded for 67.3 FD points versus the Chicago Bulls – why would we stop using centers against Chicago?", "label": [[34, 42, "DATE"], [62, 66, "CARDINAL"], [88, 101, "ORG"], [144, 151, "GPE"], [17, 30, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4314, "data": "He’s also hit 5x value in four out of his last six outings and he’s turned the ball over just twice in his previous 11 games.", "label": [[14, 16, "CARDINAL"], [47, 50, "CARDINAL"], [26, 30, "CARDINAL"], [116, 118, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4320, "data": "Bitadze just recorded 31.1 FD points on Wednesday versus the Minnesota Timberwolves in 25 minutes.", "label": [[22, 26, "CARDINAL"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [61, 83, "ORG"], [87, 97, "TIME"], [40, 49, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4326, "data": "Due to his ability to produce steals and blocks, he’s a valuable player to use on FanDuel.", "label": [[82, 89, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4332, "data": "Despite his long layoff, Anthony would play 25 minutes and was a key member of the team off of the bench.", "label": [[44, 54, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 4338, "data": "If Brogdon is sidelined for another game on Friday, then Jeremy Lamb could be set up for a productive showing against the Magic.", "label": [[44, 50, "DATE"], [122, 127, "ORG"], [57, 68, "PERSON"], [3, 10, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4344, "data": "Why not take a flier on a member of the Wizards that can put points in bunches from outside the arc?", "label": [[40, 47, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4350, "data": "Isaiah Thomas (NOP) $3,900 vs. PHI: It is awesome to see Isaiah Thomas back in the NBA as the New Orleans Pelicans have given him a chance amid their injury woes recently.", "label": [[83, 86, "ORG"], [15, 18, "ORG"], [90, 114, "ORG"], [57, 70, "PERSON"], [20, 26, "MONEY"], [31, 34, "ORG"], [0, 13, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4356, "data": "NBA players are paying their respects after Grammy-nominated hip-hop artist DMX, whose birth name was Earl Simmons, died at 50.", "label": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [124, 126, "CARDINAL"], [44, 50, "ORG"], [61, 79, "PERSON"], [102, 114, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4362, "data": "DENVER (AP) — The Denver Nuggets bolstered their backcourt by signing guard Shaquille Harrison to a two-way deal.", "label": [[18, 32, "ORG"], [0, 6, "GPE"], [76, 94, "PERSON"], [100, 103, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4368, "data": "The 27-year-old Harrison wasn’t selected in the 2016 NBA draft after a career at Tulsa in which he averaged 11.1 points and 3.5 assists.", "label": [[4, 15, "DATE"], [16, 24, "PERSON"], [48, 52, "DATE"], [53, 56, "ORG"], [108, 112, "CARDINAL"], [124, 127, "CARDINAL"], [81, 86, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4374, "data": "His most productive season was 2018-19 in Chicago when he played in 73 games and averaged 6.3 points.", "label": [[31, 38, "DATE"], [42, 49, "GPE"], [68, 70, "CARDINAL"], [90, 93, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4386, "data": "Memphis has eight players averaging at least 10 ppg, including six that have appeared in all four games.", "label": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [45, 47, "CARDINAL"], [63, 66, "CARDINAL"], [93, 97, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4392, "data": "• While the Grizzlies lead the league in points in the paint (55.6 ppg), the Knicks allow the third-fewest points in the lane (42.8 ppg).", "label": [[8, 21, "ORG"], [62, 66, "CARDINAL"], [127, 131, "CARDINAL"], [73, 83, "ORG"], [94, 99, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4398, "data": "Noel allows teams to shoot just 51.1% at the basket, matching two-time Defensive Player of the Year Rudy Gobert.", "label": [[32, 37, "PERCENT"], [0, 4, "PERSON"], [62, 65, "CARDINAL"], [100, 111, "PERSON"], [71, 99, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4404, "data": "New York’s bench players average 35.6 ppg (13th), accounting for 33.96% of the Knicks total points (9th).", "label": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [33, 37, "CARDINAL"], [43, 47, "ORDINAL"], [65, 71, "PERCENT"], [79, 85, "ORG"], [100, 103, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4416, "data": "Curry leads the NBA in 3-pointers made per game (4.7) and scores 47.3% of his points from beyond the arc, compared to 34.5% on 2-point shots and 18.2% at the free throw line.", "label": [[23, 33, "PRODUCT"], [16, 19, "ORG"], [49, 52, "CARDINAL"], [65, 70, "PERCENT"], [118, 123, "PERCENT"], [127, 134, "PRODUCT"], [145, 150, "PERCENT"], [0, 5, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4418, "data": "For Beal, he scores the majority of his points (55.9%) on 2-point shots, including 18.5% coming from mid-range (15th in NBA), only 21.5% on 3-pointers, and 22.6% at the free throw line (20th in NBA).", "label": [[140, 150, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4422, "data": "It is the longest active streak of 30-point games in the league and tied for the second-longest of the season, trailing only six straight from Beal from Jan. 6-27.", "label": [[35, 43, "PRODUCT"], [125, 128, "CARDINAL"], [143, 147, "PERSON"], [153, 162, "DATE"], [81, 87, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4428, "data": "Curry has been more consistent as he averaged 29.7 ppg (4th) in 35 games prior to the break, and 29.6 ppg in eight games since the break to lead all scorers post All-Star.", "label": [[162, 170, "PRODUCT"], [97, 101, "CARDINAL"], [46, 50, "CARDINAL"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [56, 59, "ORDINAL"], [64, 66, "CARDINAL"], [109, 114, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4434, "data": "• The Wizards (104.46) and Warriors (103.02) rank first and second in the league in pace this season.", "label": [[6, 13, "ORG"], [27, 35, "ORG"], [37, 43, "CARDINAL"], [15, 21, "CARDINAL"], [50, 55, "ORDINAL"], [60, 66, "ORDINAL"], [89, 100, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4440, "data": "Embiid checks in at No.3, in part due to James Harden and Giannis Antetokounmpo missing time this week because of injuries.", "label": [[20, 24, "ORDINAL"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [41, 53, "PERSON"], [58, 79, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4446, "data": "Embiid averaged 38.3 ppg and 9.0 rpg in the three matchups with Boston, and connected on 60.4% from the field, making him one of just three players around the league to accomplish that feat this season against the Celtics.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [16, 20, "CARDINAL"], [29, 32, "CARDINAL"], [44, 49, "CARDINAL"], [64, 70, "GPE"], [89, 94, "PERCENT"], [134, 139, "CARDINAL"], [214, 221, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4452, "data": "He’s tied at No.6 with Luka Doncic, who helped Dallas bounce back from a rough loss at Houston with a win Thursday against Milwaukee.", "label": [[13, 17, "ORDINAL"], [23, 34, "PERSON"], [47, 53, "GPE"], [87, 94, "GPE"], [106, 114, "DATE"], [123, 132, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4458, "data": "Still, it’s a wide-open race now that Embiid’s back in the mix, and as you can see here , there’s still no real consensus on the favorite to win the Kia MVP, even among some of the league’s all-time greats.", "label": [[38, 44, "PERSON"], [149, 156, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4464, "data": "The most consistent player in the field of Kia MVP candidates, Jokic put together his 18th game this season with 25 points or more and 10-plus rebounds for a Denver squad that possesses arguably the most potent offensive trio (Jokic, Murray and Michael Porter Jr.) in the league.", "label": [[43, 50, "PRODUCT"], [63, 68, "PERSON"], [113, 115, "CARDINAL"], [86, 90, "ORDINAL"], [135, 137, "CARDINAL"], [227, 232, "PERSON"], [234, 240, "PERSON"], [245, 263, "PERSON"], [158, 164, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4470, "data": "But attrition keeps Lillard in this spot, considering the missed time and injuries to Harden and Antetokounmpo, not to mention the fact he’s gutted his way through various bumps and bruises, sitting out just two games the entire season.", "label": [[20, 27, "PERSON"], [97, 110, "PERSON"], [86, 92, "PERSON"], [208, 211, "CARDINAL"], [218, 235, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4476, "data": "Last week’s ranking: No.7 Season stats: 29.9 ppg, 11.2 rpg, 3.2 apg, 1.4 bpg, 1.1 spg There’s no doubt Philadelphia welcomed back Embiid with open arms, but as colleague Shaun Powell pointed out here : The Sixers had already proven adept at winning games without the star big man.", "label": [[0, 9, "DATE"], [21, 25, "ORDINAL"], [40, 44, "CARDINAL"], [50, 54, "CARDINAL"], [60, 63, "CARDINAL"], [69, 72, "CARDINAL"], [78, 81, "CARDINAL"], [103, 115, "GPE"], [130, 136, "PERSON"], [170, 182, "PERSON"], [202, 212, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4482, "data": "Embiid claims he’s still trying to win the Kia Defensive Player of the Year , and that makes the man a terror on both ends of the floor.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [43, 75, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4488, "data": "Is Antetokounmpo’s latest injury setback cause for concern?", "label": [[3, 16, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4494, "data": "So, we’ll be consistent with Harden, considering the Nets announced Tuesday the star would be out approximately 10 days due to a right hamstring strain.", "label": [[29, 35, "PERSON"], [53, 57, "ORG"], [68, 75, "DATE"], [112, 114, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4500, "data": "The hamstring already kept Harden out of the two games prior to him tweaking it Monday against the Knicks.", "label": [[27, 33, "PERSON"], [45, 48, "CARDINAL"], [80, 86, "DATE"], [99, 105, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4506, "data": "Kyrie Irving, Brooklyn Nets 7.", "label": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [14, 27, "ORG"], [28, 29, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4512, "data": "Devin Booker, Phoenix Suns 10.", "label": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [14, 26, "ORG"], [27, 29, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4518, "data": "You can e-mail him here , find his archive here  and follow him on Twitter .", "label": [[67, 74, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4524, "data": "The team announced Thursday that Collins has progressed to drills such lateral shuffling and individual court work.", "label": [[19, 27, "DATE"], [33, 40, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4530, "data": "He underwent an MRI that showed a lateral ankle sprain and associated bone bruise.", "label": [[16, 19, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4536, "data": "He was as doubtful leading up to the Bucks-Mavs showdown, which Milwaukee lost 116-101 .", "label": [[79, 86, "SCORE"], [37, 42, "ORG"], [43, 47, "ORG"], [64, 73, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4542, "data": "Milwaukee concluded a six-game, 11-day road trip with a physically taxing loss in Dallas.", "label": [[0, 9, "GPE"], [22, 25, "CARDINAL"], [32, 34, "CARDINAL"], [82, 88, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4548, "data": "Lakers (32-19) at Heat (26-25)  7:30 p.m.", "label": [[0, 6, "ORG"], [18, 22, "ORG"], [8, 13, "SCORE"], [24, 29, "SCORE"]]}
{"id": 4554, "data": "• The Lakers were shorthanded in the first meeting as Anthony Davis and Dennis Schroder missed the game, and will be shorthanded again on Thursday as Davis and LeBron James will be out of the lineup.", "label": [[6, 12, "ORG"], [37, 42, "ORDINAL"], [54, 67, "PERSON"], [72, 87, "PERSON"], [138, 146, "DATE"], [150, 155, "PERSON"], [160, 172, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4560, "data": "• Los Angeles’ Montrezl Harrell (15.0 ppg) and Miami’s Tyler Herro (14.7 ppg) rank fourth and fifth, respectively, in bench scoring this season.", "label": [[2, 13, "GPE"], [47, 52, "GPE"], [15, 31, "PERSON"], [33, 37, "CARDINAL"], [55, 66, "PERSON"], [68, 72, "CARDINAL"], [83, 89, "ORDINAL"], [94, 99, "ORDINAL"], [132, 143, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4566, "data": "The Heat at 22-14 with Butler in the lineup this season, and just 4-11 in the games he has missed.", "label": [[4, 8, "ORG"], [12, 17, "SCORE"], [66, 70, "SCORE"], [44, 55, "DATE"], [23, 29, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4572, "data": "Suns (36-14) at Clippers (34-18)  10 p.m.", "label": [[0, 4, "ORG"], [16, 24, "ORG"], [6, 11, "SCORE"], [26, 31, "SCORE"], [34, 41, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 4578, "data": "This will be Phoenix’s 12th game on the second night of a back-to-back; they are 9-2 in such games so far this season, with an average point differential of plus-10.2 ppg.", "label": [[13, 20, "GPE"], [23, 27, "ORDINAL"], [40, 46, "ORDINAL"], [58, 70, "PRODUCT"], [81, 84, "SCORE"], [106, 117, "DATE"], [157, 166, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4584, "data": "George scored the majority of his points while matched up with either Devin Booker (9 points on 4-4 FG, 1-1 3FG in 3:32 of matchup time) or Deandre Ayton (123 points on 5-6 FG, 3-4 3FG in 1:28 of matchup time).", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [70, 82, "PERSON"], [84, 85, "CARDINAL"], [96, 99, "SCORE"], [104, 107, "SCORE"], [115, 119, "TIME"], [140, 153, "PERSON"], [155, 158, "CARDINAL"], [169, 172, "SCORE"], [177, 180, "SCORE"], [188, 192, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 4590, "data": "Booker had seven points on 1-2 3FG, 4-5 FT in 3:01 against Paul George.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [11, 16, "CARDINAL"], [27, 30, "SCORE"], [36, 39, "SCORE"], [46, 50, "TIME"], [59, 70, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4596, "data": "Since then, the Suns have gone 27-6 – the top record in the NBA during that time, followed by Utah and Brooklyn both a 24-8.", "label": [[16, 20, "ORG"], [31, 35, "SCORE"], [42, 45, "ORDINAL"], [60, 63, "ORG"], [119, 123, "SCORE"], [103, 111, "GPE"], [94, 98, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4602, "data": "Over Phoenix’s last 33 games, Booker has averaged 27.5 points (8th in NBA) on 20.2 shots per game and shot 50.3% from the field.", "label": [[20, 22, "CARDINAL"], [30, 36, "ORG"], [63, 66, "ORDINAL"], [70, 73, "ORG"], [78, 82, "CARDINAL"], [107, 112, "PERCENT"], [50, 54, "PERCENT"], [5, 12, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4608, "data": "Currently in his 10th season with Golden State, Welts has spent 46 seasons overall in the NBA, including roles with three teams—the Seattle SuperSonics, Phoenix Suns and the Warriors—and the NBA league office.", "label": [[17, 21, "ORDINAL"], [34, 46, "ORG"], [48, 53, "PERSON"], [64, 66, "CARDINAL"], [90, 93, "ORG"], [116, 121, "CARDINAL"], [132, 151, "ORG"], [153, 165, "ORG"], [174, 182, "ORG"], [191, 194, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4614, "data": "Welts will remain associated with the organization as an Advisor.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4620, "data": "“To have had a front row seat to the growth of the NBA from where it was in the late 1960s to its place today as one of the most respected and successful leagues in sports on a global stage has been an incredible privilege.", "label": [[51, 54, "ORG"], [85, 90, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4632, "data": "“On that day, he noted the Warriors franchise was always viewed as a sleeping giant that could be very successful if it ever got into the right hands.", "label": [[27, 35, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4638, "data": "“Fortunately, we found that 10 years ago in Rick Welts.", "label": [[28, 40, "DATE"], [44, 54, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4650, "data": "I had the tremendous good fortune to learn about the business of the NBA and its teams directly from Rick in my early years at the league office and have always appreciated his friendship and generosity.", "label": [[69, 72, "ORG"], [101, 105, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4656, "data": "Additionally, the Warriors became the first professional team to win Sports Business Journal’s “Sports Team of the Year” award on multiple occasions under Welts (2014 and 2016).", "label": [[18, 26, "ORG"], [69, 92, "ORG"], [96, 119, "PRODUCT"], [155, 160, "PERSON"], [162, 166, "DATE"], [171, 175, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4662, "data": "Welts began his NBA career as a ballboy with the SuperSonics in 1969 at the age of 16 and, a decade later, was a part of the franchise’s lone NBA championship in 1979 as its public relations director.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [16, 19, "ORG"], [64, 68, "DATE"], [49, 60, "ORG"], [83, 85, "CARDINAL"], [142, 145, "ORG"], [162, 166, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4668, "data": "Along with Val Ackerman, he was named “Marketer of the Year” by Brandweek in 1998 for his role in launching the WNBA.", "label": [[77, 81, "DATE"], [112, 116, "ORG"], [39, 59, "PRODUCT"], [11, 23, "PERSON"], [64, 73, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4674, "data": "Additionally, his teams made a total of seven NBA Finals appearances.", "label": [[46, 56, "ORG"], [40, 45, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4680, "data": "When it comes to NBA defense, there’s the scheme and there’s the energy and communication within the scheme.", "label": [[17, 20, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4692, "data": "Here are some examples of the work the Suns put in on Wednesday: 1.", "label": [[39, 43, "ORG"], [54, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4698, "data": "Deandre Ayton rotated over to contest Mitchell’s floater and Devin Booker rotated down to box out Rudy Gobert.", "label": [[61, 73, "PERSON"], [98, 109, "PERSON"], [0, 13, "PERSON"], [38, 46, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4710, "data": "Early in the third quarter, Booker was able to get over Gobert’s initial screen for Mitchell, but got hit by the second one.", "label": [[28, 34, "PERSON"], [84, 92, "PERSON"], [113, 119, "ORDINAL"], [9, 26, "DATE"], [56, 62, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4716, "data": "Forced to switch For the most part, the Suns do not want Ayton switching screens and being put on an island against an opposing guard.", "label": [[40, 44, "ORG"], [57, 62, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4722, "data": "There have been multiple occasions this season where he’s been burned badly trying to defend guards or wings one-on-one late in games, and there was another in overtime on Wednesday.", "label": [[172, 181, "DATE"], [35, 46, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4728, "data": "Joe Ingles didn’t want to shoot the seemingly open corner 3-pointer off the low catch, but Bogdanovic hit another tough shot over Booker.", "label": [[58, 67, "PRODUCT"], [0, 10, "PERSON"], [91, 101, "PERSON"], [130, 136, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4740, "data": "The Suns’ execution down the stretch on Wednesday was a little better on offense (24 points on 19 clutch possessions) than defense (where the Jazz scored 20 on 17).", "label": [[4, 8, "ORG"], [40, 49, "DATE"], [82, 84, "CARDINAL"], [95, 97, "CARDINAL"], [142, 146, "ORG"], [154, 162, "SCORE"]]}
{"id": 4746, "data": "The Jazz remain the only team in the top five in both offensive and defensive efficiency, but the Suns aren’t far behind, ranking seventh and fifth .", "label": [[4, 8, "ORG"], [98, 102, "ORG"], [142, 147, "ORDINAL"], [130, 137, "ORDINAL"], [37, 45, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4752, "data": "In the three seasons prior to coach Monty Williams’ arrival in Phoenix, the Suns ranked 28th , 30th and 29th on defense, so this has been quite the two-year turnaround.", "label": [[3, 20, "DATE"], [36, 50, "PERSON"], [63, 70, "GPE"], [76, 80, "ORG"], [88, 108, "ORDINAL"], [148, 156, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4758, "data": "It was the highest mark for any player who averaged at least five ball-handler possessions in the 16 years of Synergy tracking.", "label": [[52, 65, "CARDINAL"], [94, 106, "DATE"], [110, 117, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4760, "data": "This season, that mark is being topped, not by Lillard or one of the other guards who liberally launch long 3-pointers off the dribble, but by Kawhi Leonard.", "label": [[108, 118, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4764, "data": "While teammate Paul George has been one of the league’s best pull-up 3-point shooters this season, Leonard’s 30-for-94 (32%) on pull-up 3-pointers ranks just 47th among 62 players who’ve attempted at least 75.", "label": [[136, 146, "PRODUCT"], [69, 76, "PRODUCT"], [15, 26, "PERSON"], [109, 118, "SCORE"], [120, 123, "SCORE"], [169, 171, "CARDINAL"], [158, 162, "ORDINAL"], [197, 208, "CARDINAL"], [99, 106, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4770, "data": "With the departure of Montrezl Harrell, the Clippers have seen a big drop in the percentage of their shots that have come from the restricted area.", "label": [[22, 38, "PERSON"], [44, 52, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4776, "data": "His 6.0 ball-handler possessions per game are down from 8.4 last season and rank just 37th in the league , right behind Elfrid Payton (0.86 points per possession).", "label": [[4, 7, "CARDINAL"], [56, 59, "CARDINAL"], [60, 71, "DATE"], [86, 90, "ORDINAL"], [120, 133, "PERSON"], [135, 139, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4782, "data": "They’re 4-2 over that stretch so far , though one of the two losses came in the game (vs. Orlando) that wasn’t against one of the good teams.", "label": [[8, 11, "SCORE"], [90, 97, "ORG"], [119, 122, "CARDINAL"], [57, 60, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4800, "data": "This season, under new coach Billy Donovan, the Bulls are at the other end of the list.", "label": [[0, 11, "DATE"], [29, 42, "PERSON"], [48, 53, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4806, "data": "The team where the Bulls were last year is the Charlotte Hornets, with only 10.6% of Charlotte opponent possessions having been pick-and-roll ball-handler possessions.", "label": [[19, 24, "ORG"], [30, 39, "DATE"], [47, 64, "ORG"], [76, 81, "PERCENT"], [85, 94, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4812, "data": "One, the Hornets have defended the fewest ball screens per 100 possessions, according to Second Spectrum tracking.", "label": [[59, 62, "CARDINAL"], [9, 16, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4818, "data": "After Charlotte, the teams with the lowest rates are Miami (Bam Adebayo liberally switches ball screens), Toronto, Denver and Indiana.", "label": [[6, 15, "GPE"], [53, 58, "GPE"], [106, 113, "GPE"], [115, 121, "GPE"], [126, 133, "GPE"], [60, 71, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4830, "data": "When the Celtics went to a 2-3 zone, the Sixers might not have recognized it, so they ran their play, and it turned out to work really well … When Tobias Harris and Joel Embiid set a staggered screen for Seth Curry, Jayson Tatum had to slide over from the left side of the floor to pick up the ball.", "label": [[9, 16, "GPE"], [27, 30, "SCORE"], [41, 47, "ORG"], [147, 160, "PERSON"], [165, 176, "PERSON"], [204, 214, "PERSON"], [216, 228, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4836, "data": "If the Celtics were given another chance to defend the same play, they’d probably have Jaylen Brown rotate into the middle of the paint to deny the pass to Embiid, so that the only uncovered Sixer was Harris, a long pass away from Green.", "label": [[7, 14, "ORG"], [87, 99, "PERSON"], [156, 162, "PERSON"], [191, 196, "ORG"], [201, 207, "PERSON"], [231, 236, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4842, "data": "The Nets don’t seem to mind if James Harden gets switched onto a big.", "label": [[4, 8, "ORG"], [31, 43, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4848, "data": "There were two back-to-back examples of this in the Nets’ blowout win over New Orleans on Wednesday.", "label": [[52, 56, "ORG"], [75, 86, "GPE"], [90, 99, "DATE"], [11, 14, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4854, "data": "Irving was a little slow to rotate to Johnson, but the Pels’ forward had no interest in shooting an open 3-pointer and, when he drove, Irving poked the ball away … On the next possession, Lonzo Ball set a ball-screen for Zion Williamson.", "label": [[105, 114, "PRODUCT"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [38, 45, "PERSON"], [55, 59, "PERSON"], [135, 141, "PERSON"], [188, 198, "PERSON"], [221, 236, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4860, "data": "Durant rotated down to Jaxson Hayes and Irving rotated out to Johnson.", "label": [[62, 69, "PERSON"], [0, 6, "PERSON"], [23, 35, "PERSON"], [40, 46, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4862, "data": "He was slow getting there again, but Johnson missed an open 3-pointer … With the Nets’ switching scheme, opponents will continue to look for matchups they can take advantage of.", "label": [[60, 69, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4868, "data": "* * * John Schuhmann is a senior stats analyst for NBA.com.", "label": [[6, 20, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4872, "data": "The views on this page do not necessarily reflect the views of the NBA, its clubs or Turner Broadcasting.", "label": [[67, 70, "ORG"], [85, 104, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4878, "data": "Anunoby, who received a technical foul and was ejected, has been fined $30,000 for initiating the incident by grabbing Schröder by the leg and recklessly flipping him to the ground after the two became entangled following a common foul committed by Schröder.", "label": [[71, 78, "MONEY"], [119, 127, "PERSON"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [249, 257, "PERSON"], [191, 194, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4884, "data": "Bembry will serve his suspension tonight when the Raptors play host to the Chicago Bulls at Amalie Arena.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [33, 40, "DATE"], [75, 88, "ORG"], [92, 104, "GPE"], [50, 57, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4896, "data": "Vogel said after the Lakers beat the Toronto Raptors on Tuesday that Drummond would start once he was cleared to play again.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [37, 52, "ORG"], [56, 63, "DATE"], [69, 77, "PERSON"], [21, 27, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4902, "data": "He started for the Lakers in his first NBA game in 6 1/2 weeks, but he wasn’t on the floor to start the second half while getting treatment on his toe.", "label": [[39, 42, "ORG"], [51, 56, "CARDINAL"], [19, 25, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4908, "data": "Additionally, forward Kyle Kuzma (calf tightness) is listed as questionable against the Heat while new swingman Ben McLemore will be available to play against Miami.", "label": [[22, 32, "PERSON"], [88, 92, "ORG"], [112, 124, "PERSON"], [159, 164, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4914, "data": "Davis has not played since Feb. 14 because of an Achilles injury, while James (ankle) has been out since March 21.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [72, 77, "PERSON"], [27, 34, "DATE"], [105, 113, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4920, "data": "While paying up for De’Aaron Fox should be a popular choice, Harrison Barnes could be a nice mid-tier option at the power forward position.", "label": [[20, 32, "PERSON"], [61, 76, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4926, "data": "Kyle Lowry was ruled out 7-10 days over a week ago, but it would be a surprise to see him suit up on Thursday.", "label": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [25, 29, "SCORE"], [40, 50, "DATE"], [101, 109, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4932, "data": "The Bulls have allowed a league-high 61.75 FD points per game to centers in their past 30 games.", "label": [[4, 9, "ORG"], [37, 42, "CARDINAL"], [87, 89, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4938, "data": "He has seen 30+ minutes in his past three games, and he should easily hit 5x value at his $6,000 price tag as long as VanVleet and Lowry are both confirmed out again.", "label": [[12, 23, "TIME"], [36, 41, "CARDINAL"], [74, 76, "CARDINAL"], [90, 96, "MONEY"], [118, 126, "PERSON"], [131, 136, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4944, "data": "Prince has taken Cedi Osman‘s spot in the rotation, playing in 25+ minutes in the past two games, where he scored 30+ FD points in both games.", "label": [[17, 27, "PERSON"], [63, 74, "TIME"], [87, 90, "CARDINAL"], [114, 116, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4950, "data": "For the Jazz, Jordan Clarkson is a way to get a piece of Utah’s roster for a reasonable price.", "label": [[8, 12, "ORG"], [14, 29, "PERSON"], [57, 61, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 4956, "data": "DeAndre’ Bembry (TOR) $5,200 vs. CHI Once again, the Raptors are expected to be extremely shorthanded again on Thursday, which means there is value to be had.", "label": [[53, 60, "ORG"], [111, 119, "DATE"], [22, 28, "MONEY"], [0, 15, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "ORG"], [33, 36, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 4962, "data": "The veteran guard has also posted 34+ FD points in back-to-back games.", "label": [[34, 37, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 4968, "data": "That could set up Moses Brown for a massive role on Thursday.", "label": [[52, 60, "DATE"], [18, 29, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4974, "data": "Nevertheless, the rookie forward gets an opportunity to face a shorthanded Toronto squad on Thursday, which could pave the way for him to receive more minutes.", "label": [[75, 82, "GPE"], [92, 100, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 4980, "data": "Isaiah Hartenstein (CLE) $4,000 at OKC Due to Allen and Nance being out, the Cavaliers are left with Prince, Kevin Love, Dean Wade, and Isaiah Hartenstein in the frontcourt.", "label": [[0, 18, "PERSON"], [20, 23, "ORG"], [25, 31, "MONEY"], [35, 38, "ORG"], [46, 51, "PERSON"], [56, 61, "PERSON"], [77, 86, "ORG"], [101, 107, "PERSON"], [109, 119, "PERSON"], [121, 130, "PERSON"], [136, 154, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 4986, "data": "Svi Mykhailiuk (OKC) $3,800 vs. CLE When looking for a player sub-$3,000, Svi Mykhailiuk could be a notable option at the shooting guard position.", "label": [[16, 19, "ORG"], [0, 14, "PERSON"], [22, 27, "MONEY"], [32, 35, "ORG"], [74, 88, "PERSON"], [67, 72, "MONEY"]]}
{"id": 4992, "data": "The Brooklyn Nets got one of their All-Stars back in the mix even as another one rests.", "label": [[4, 17, "ORG"], [35, 44, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 4998, "data": "He shot a perfect 5-for-5 for the field, finishing with 17 points, seven rebounds, and five assists.", "label": [[18, 25, "SCORE"], [56, 58, "CARDINAL"], [67, 72, "CARDINAL"], [87, 91, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5004, "data": "“I wasn’t trying to ease into the game.” Coach Steve Nash said bringing Durant off the bench was so the Nets could more easily control his minutes if the game was close down the stretch.", "label": [[47, 57, "PERSON"], [72, 78, "PERSON"], [104, 108, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5010, "data": "Totally dominated,” Pelicans coach Stan Van Gundy said.", "label": [[35, 49, "PERSON"], [20, 28, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5012, "data": "“We couldn’t get out to the 3-point line.", "label": [[28, 35, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5016, "data": "They totally dominated us.” Durant got an ovation from the first home crowd he’d played in front of with the Nets.", "label": [[28, 34, "PERSON"], [59, 64, "ORDINAL"], [109, 113, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5022, "data": "He wasn’t able to start on Feb. 5 against Toronto in what was his 867th game while the NBA reviewed an inconclusive coronavirus test result of someone Durant had interacted with that afternoon.", "label": [[27, 33, "DATE"], [42, 49, "GPE"], [66, 71, "ORDINAL"], [87, 90, "ORG"], [151, 157, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5028, "data": "“The last month or so, it’s just been me working out every day, playing here and there with my teammates,” Durant said.", "label": [[107, 113, "PERSON"], [1, 15, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5034, "data": "Durant is averaging 29.0 ppg, 7.3 rpg and 5.9 apg for the Nets this season.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [20, 24, "CARDINAL"], [30, 33, "CARDINAL"], [42, 45, "CARDINAL"], [58, 62, "ORG"], [63, 74, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5038, "data": "Harden originally sustained the injury on March 31 against the Houston Rockets but appeared to reaggravate the hamstring in his return against the New York Knicks on Monday.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [42, 50, "DATE"], [166, 172, "DATE"], [143, 162, "ORG"], [59, 78, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5040, "data": "He lasted just four minutes before having to exit the contest.", "label": [[15, 27, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 5046, "data": "He averaged 40.7 FanDuel points per game (FDPPG) through that stretch (5.6x value), and he’ll take on the NBA’s worst defense against centers this evening.", "label": [[12, 16, "CARDINAL"], [42, 47, "PRODUCT"], [71, 75, "CARDINAL"], [106, 109, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5052, "data": "The Pacers held Brogdon out of last night’s game because of a hip injury, but he was able to practice on Monday.", "label": [[4, 10, "ORG"], [16, 23, "PERSON"], [31, 41, "DATE"], [105, 111, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5058, "data": "Devonte’ Graham (CHA) $6,500 The Hornets are now without LaMelo Ball, Malik Monk and Gordon Hayward.", "label": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [17, 20, "ORG"], [22, 28, "MONEY"], [33, 40, "ORG"], [57, 68, "PERSON"], [70, 80, "PERSON"], [85, 99, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5064, "data": "I prefer Graham to Terry Rozier ($7,400) simply because of the price differential.", "label": [[9, 15, "PERSON"], [19, 31, "PERSON"], [33, 39, "MONEY"]]}
{"id": 5070, "data": "But Barrett lit up Boston for 19 points, three assists and 11 rebounds back in January, so we can’t write him off.", "label": [[4, 11, "ORG"], [19, 25, "GPE"], [30, 32, "CARDINAL"], [41, 46, "CARDINAL"], [59, 61, "CARDINAL"], [79, 86, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5076, "data": "Aleksej Pokusevski (OKC) $5,500 With Isaiah Roby, Luguentz Dort, Shai Gilgeous-Alexander and Darius Bazley all still out for the Thunder, the team’s reserves will have to keep stepping up.", "label": [[0, 18, "PERSON"], [37, 48, "PERSON"], [20, 23, "ORG"], [25, 31, "MONEY"], [50, 63, "PERSON"], [65, 88, "PERSON"], [93, 106, "PERSON"], [129, 136, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5088, "data": "Also, the Thunder allow the second-most FDPPG to opposing power forwards.", "label": [[10, 17, "ORG"], [40, 45, "PRODUCT"], [28, 34, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5094, "data": "Richardson hit 5x value against this price in his last appearance, and this is the perfect opponent for him to start building some momentum.", "label": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [15, 17, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5100, "data": "Kevin Durant should make his return tonight, but since James Harden will have to miss time with a hamstring injury, Harris should still have plenty of chances to hit value.", "label": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [55, 67, "PERSON"], [116, 122, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5106, "data": "He played just 12.8 minutes per game through that stretch.", "label": [[15, 27, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 5112, "data": "He played 20-plus minutes in his first two games back for the Wizards (of course, Bradley Beal has been out), but he should be in line for a stable rotational role behind even if they both play; he had been averaging 20.6 minutes per game before his injury.", "label": [[10, 25, "TIME"], [62, 69, "ORG"], [33, 38, "ORDINAL"], [39, 42, "CARDINAL"], [82, 94, "PERSON"], [217, 229, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 5118, "data": "Anyone who has returned a confirmed positive test, or has been identified as having been in close contact to an infected person, is isolated or quarantined until they are cleared under the rules established by the NBA and the Players Association in accordance with CDC guidance.", "label": [[214, 217, "ORG"], [226, 245, "ORG"], [265, 268, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5124, "data": "“I am forever thankful to God for blessing me with talents, surrounding me with a solid support system and positioning me to take this next big step,” Johnson wrote.", "label": [[26, 29, "PERSON"], [151, 158, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5130, "data": "The 6-foot-5, 186-pound Johnson started 17 games and was the second-leading scorer, averaging 11.3 points a game.", "label": [[4, 12, "CARDINAL"], [14, 17, "CARDINAL"], [24, 31, "PERSON"], [40, 42, "CARDINAL"], [61, 67, "ORDINAL"], [94, 98, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5142, "data": "Such as the Golden State Warriors, more so maybe than most.", "label": [[12, 33, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5148, "data": "(Klay Thompson’s is ticking too in the rehab gym.)", "label": [[1, 14, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5154, "data": "The 7-footer who logged just three appearances in his brief stint of college ball at Memphis was precocious to start this season, averaging 12.2 points and 6.1 rebounds through January.", "label": [[140, 144, "CARDINAL"], [156, 159, "CARDINAL"], [177, 184, "DATE"], [85, 92, "PERSON"], [117, 128, "DATE"], [4, 12, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5166, "data": "Add in the Warriors’ vaunted culture and peer mentoring, presumably shortening the young man’s learning curve (he turned 20 last week), and many folks naturally focused on Wiseman.", "label": [[124, 133, "DATE"], [172, 179, "PERSON"], [11, 19, "ORG"], [121, 123, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5172, "data": "He noted that of the eight centers who won the award over the past 50 years, six had more college experience than Wiseman and one (Pau Gasol) had been a pro for two years in Spain.", "label": [[131, 140, "PERSON"], [161, 164, "CARDINAL"], [174, 179, "GPE"], [58, 75, "DATE"], [77, 80, "CARDINAL"], [114, 121, "PERSON"], [21, 26, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5178, "data": "“He’s going to need a summer league and a training camp next year.", "label": [[56, 65, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5184, "data": "As Kerr said: “There are moments when he looks like a future superstar.", "label": [[3, 7, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5190, "data": "He continues to lead the rookies in scoring ( 17.6 ) and in shots per game ( 16.5 ).", "label": [[46, 50, "CARDINAL"], [77, 81, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5196, "data": "It’s looking like it will take something dramatic for a new face to crack the Top 2 here, though Edwards and Haliburton could flip-flop repeatedly down the stretch.", "label": [[78, 83, "CARDINAL"], [97, 104, "PERSON"], [109, 119, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5202, "data": "He has averaged 12 points and 5.5 assists to one turnover, shooting 43.5% in the losses, while managing a combined plus-10 in the past two.", "label": [[16, 18, "CARDINAL"], [30, 33, "CARDINAL"], [68, 73, "PERCENT"], [130, 138, "DATE"], [115, 122, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5208, "data": "You can answer for yourself, based on his two-way play, counting stats and 52.3 FG%.", "label": [[75, 83, "PERCENT"]]}
{"id": 5214, "data": "Season stats : 10.5 ppg, 4.0 rpg, 1.3 apg Since last Ladder: 9.2 ppg, 2.8 rpg, 1.6 apg  Last Ladder’s rung : 5 His accuracy sagged last week – 39.7% overall – until his 9-of-15 (6-of-12 from the arc) for 25 points Tuesday at Denver.", "label": [[15, 19, "CARDINAL"], [25, 28, "CARDINAL"], [34, 37, "CARDINAL"], [169, 176, "SCORE"], [178, 185, "SCORE"], [204, 206, "CARDINAL"], [214, 221, "DATE"], [225, 231, "GPE"], [143, 148, "PERCENT"], [61, 64, "CARDINAL"], [79, 82, "CARDINAL"], [70, 73, "CARDINAL"], [131, 140, "DATE"], [109, 110, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5220, "data": "Season stats : 12.2 ppg, 2.3 rpg, 2.2 apg Since last Ladder: 6.6 ppg, 2.2 rpg, 1.4 apg  Last Ladder’s rung : 3 It could be a slump, it could be the rookie wall.", "label": [[15, 19, "CARDINAL"], [25, 28, "CARDINAL"], [34, 37, "CARDINAL"], [61, 64, "CARDINAL"], [70, 73, "CARDINAL"], [79, 82, "CARDINAL"], [109, 110, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5238, "data": "James Wiseman, Golden State Warriors Season stats : 11.4 ppg, 5.8 rpg, 0.6 apg Since last Ladder: 8.3 ppg, 4.8 rpg, 0.8 apg  Last Ladder’s rung : 7 Roller-coaster continues, from big dip week to fresh ascendancy?", "label": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [15, 36, "ORG"], [52, 56, "CARDINAL"], [71, 74, "CARDINAL"], [62, 65, "CARDINAL"], [98, 101, "CARDINAL"], [107, 110, "CARDINAL"], [116, 119, "CARDINAL"], [146, 147, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5250, "data": "Theo Maledon, Oklahoma City Thunder Season stats : 9.4 ppg, 3.5 rpg, 3.3 apg Since last Ladder: 15.8 ppg, 5.2 rpg, 2.4 apg  Last Ladder’s rung : N/A Showing Euro experience now as OKC plays for the future.", "label": [[14, 35, "ORG"], [0, 12, "PERSON"], [51, 54, "CARDINAL"], [60, 63, "CARDINAL"], [69, 72, "CARDINAL"], [96, 100, "CARDINAL"], [106, 109, "CARDINAL"], [115, 118, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5256, "data": "The views on this page do not necessarily reflect the views of the NBA, its clubs or Turner Broadcasting.", "label": [[67, 70, "ORG"], [85, 104, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5262, "data": "That number won’t change for at least 10 days as Harden is out with a hamstring strain, while Durant is available to play after suffering a hamstring injury of his own that kept him out seven weeks.", "label": [[94, 100, "PERSON"], [186, 197, "DATE"], [38, 45, "DATE"], [49, 55, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5268, "data": "In the 23 games that he’s missed during that time, the Nets went an NBA-best 19-4 while averaging 115.8 ppg and outscoring teams by an average of 5.5 ppg.", "label": [[7, 9, "CARDINAL"], [55, 59, "ORG"], [68, 71, "ORG"], [77, 81, "SCORE"], [98, 103, "CARDINAL"], [146, 149, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5274, "data": "• New Orleans is coming off a 123-107 loss to Atlanta on Tuesday; this season the Pelicans are 3-6 on the second night of a back-to-back.", "label": [[2, 13, "GPE"], [30, 37, "SCORE"], [46, 53, "GPE"], [57, 64, "DATE"], [66, 77, "DATE"], [95, 98, "SCORE"], [106, 112, "ORDINAL"], [82, 90, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5280, "data": "• Brooklyn enters Wednesday ranked sixth in 3-pointers made (14.2 per game) and fourth in 3-point accuracy (39.1%).", "label": [[44, 54, "PRODUCT"], [90, 97, "PRODUCT"], [2, 10, "GPE"], [18, 27, "DATE"], [35, 40, "ORDINAL"], [61, 65, "CARDINAL"], [108, 113, "PERCENT"], [80, 86, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5282, "data": "The Nets’ team 3-point percentage gets a strong boost from Joe Harris, who ranks third in the league in 3-point shooting (48.4%) and fifth in total 3-pointers made (164).", "label": [[15, 22, "PRODUCT"], [148, 158, "PRODUCT"], [104, 111, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5286, "data": "ET, ESPN • With Utah’s nine-game win streak snapped on Monday, the Suns are tied with Denver for the longest active win streak in the league (six straight).", "label": [[23, 27, "CARDINAL"], [55, 61, "DATE"], [67, 71, "ORG"], [86, 92, "GPE"], [142, 145, "CARDINAL"], [16, 20, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5292, "data": "• The Jazz lead the NBA with 43.6% of their points coming from 3-pointers.", "label": [[63, 73, "PRODUCT"], [6, 10, "ORG"], [20, 23, "ORG"], [29, 34, "PERCENT"]]}
{"id": 5294, "data": "Utah shoots 39.5% from 3-point range (2nd in the NBA) and averages a league-high 17 3-pointers made per game.", "label": [[23, 30, "PRODUCT"], [84, 94, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5298, "data": "• While Utah is shooting 3-pointers at a historic pace, the Suns are one of the top teams in defending the 3-point shot .", "label": [[25, 35, "PRODUCT"], [107, 114, "PRODUCT"], [8, 12, "GPE"], [60, 64, "ORG"], [69, 72, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5300, "data": "Phoenix holds teams to 34.8% shooting from beyond the arc (fourth-lowest percentage allowed) and just 32.6 3-point attempts per game (ninth-fewest in the league).", "label": [[0, 7, "ORG"], [23, 28, "PERCENT"], [59, 72, "ORDINAL"], [102, 106, "CARDINAL"], [107, 114, "PRODUCT"], [134, 146, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5304, "data": "• The Suns and Jazz are both 11-3 since the All-Star break, tied with Brooklyn and Denver for the top record in the league since the break.", "label": [[15, 19, "ORG"], [29, 33, "SCORE"], [70, 78, "GPE"], [83, 89, "GPE"], [2, 10, "ORG"], [44, 52, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5310, "data": "“I don’t know if anyone could have saw this vision a year ago or two years ago,” Irving said last week , after Brooklyn’s 111-89 win against the Charlotte Hornets.", "label": [[51, 61, "DATE"], [65, 78, "DATE"], [81, 87, "PERSON"], [111, 119, "GPE"], [122, 128, "SCORE"], [145, 162, "ORG"], [93, 102, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5316, "data": "You’ve got to make some major moves, and we made some major changes this year.", "label": [[68, 77, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5322, "data": "We’re literally dedicated to performing the craft of basketball at a very high level for one another because we want to see each other win.” Irving embodied that last statement throughout March by tweaking his game, after virtually handing James Harden the keys to Brooklyn’s offense to help the piecemeal Nets (without Kevin Durant in the lineup) roll to an 11-2 mark last month.", "label": [[141, 147, "PERSON"], [188, 193, "DATE"], [240, 252, "PERSON"], [265, 273, "GPE"], [306, 310, "ORG"], [320, 332, "PERSON"], [359, 363, "SCORE"], [369, 379, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5328, "data": "The Nets are preparing to host New Orleans on Wednesday without Harden (hamstring), who is expected to miss at least 10 days, while Durant is available to play after he missed 23 consecutive contests.", "label": [[4, 8, "ORG"], [31, 42, "GPE"], [46, 55, "DATE"], [64, 70, "PERSON"], [117, 124, "DATE"], [132, 138, "PERSON"], [176, 178, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5334, "data": "“He’s just an amazing basketball player, and he found a way to keep our team in it for big stretches,” Nets coach Steve Nash said of Irving.", "label": [[103, 107, "ORG"], [114, 124, "PERSON"], [133, 139, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5340, "data": "Keep in mind the Nets opened the contest without Durant, Tyler Johnson (right knee), Landry Shamet (right ankle) and Blake Griffin (left knee injury management), before losing Harden (who logged a little more than four minutes).", "label": [[85, 98, "PERSON"], [117, 130, "PERSON"], [17, 21, "ORG"], [49, 55, "PERSON"], [57, 70, "PERSON"], [176, 182, "PERSON"], [214, 226, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 5346, "data": "“I think we’ve all won enough individually,” Irving said last week.", "label": [[45, 51, "PERSON"], [57, 66, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5358, "data": "Harden had already missed his second consecutive game with the hamstring issue on Sunday, before reinjuring it against the Knicks.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [82, 88, "DATE"], [123, 129, "ORG"], [30, 36, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5364, "data": "We have to just come together collectively and figure out ways to win.” Added Irving: “It’s tough to move onto the next thing after one of our guys goes down with an injury, an apparent injury where they have to go to the back.” Yet that’s what Irving and the Nets continue to do.", "label": [[78, 84, "PERSON"], [132, 135, "CARDINAL"], [245, 251, "PERSON"], [260, 264, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5370, "data": "Durant, meanwhile, hasn’t played since Feb. 13.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"], [39, 46, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5376, "data": "“Well, shoot, I’d rather not think about it,” Irving said.", "label": [[46, 52, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5394, "data": "NEW YORK — Today, the National Basketball Association (NBA) and CLEAR, the secure identity company, announced a partnership that will make CLEAR’s Health Pass technology available to NBA teams for COVID-19 health screenings in their arenas.", "label": [[0, 8, "GPE"], [11, 16, "DATE"], [22, 53, "ORG"], [55, 58, "ORG"], [64, 69, "ORG"], [183, 186, "ORG"], [197, 205, "PRODUCT"], [139, 144, "ORG"], [147, 169, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5400, "data": "CLEAR’s Health Pass allows fans to securely access and verify their health information prior to entering an arena.", "label": [[0, 5, "ORG"], [8, 19, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5406, "data": "“As states reopen sports venues to fans in the U.S., we are thrilled to team up with the NBA to help create safer fan experiences and reimagine the future of sports.” “CLEAR’s Health Pass is an innovative technology that can further enhance the league’s health and safety protocols at arenas and the wellbeing of those who attend NBA games,” said Dan Rossomondo, NBA Senior Vice President, Media & Business Development.", "label": [[89, 92, "ORG"], [168, 173, "ORG"], [330, 333, "ORG"], [347, 361, "PERSON"], [363, 366, "ORG"], [176, 187, "PRODUCT"], [47, 51, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5412, "data": "Health Pass builds upon CLEAR’s history of creating frictionless experiences in sports, including innovative pilots for touchless ticketing, biometric payments and age validation.", "label": [[24, 29, "ORG"], [0, 11, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5418, "data": "McLemore appeared in 32 games (four starts) for Houston this season, averaging 7.4 points, 2.1 rebounds and 0.9 assists in 16.8 minutes per game.", "label": [[0, 8, "PERSON"], [21, 23, "CARDINAL"], [48, 55, "GPE"], [79, 82, "CARDINAL"], [91, 94, "CARDINAL"], [108, 111, "CARDINAL"], [123, 135, "TIME"], [56, 67, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5424, "data": "NBA Commissioner Adam Silver said in March that changes to the league’s health and safety protocols would be in store for those who decide to get the vaccine.", "label": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [17, 28, "PERSON"], [37, 42, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5430, "data": "Harden originally sustained the injury on March 31 against the Houston Rockets but appeared to reaggravate the hamstring in his return against the New York Knicks on Monday.", "label": [[143, 162, "ORG"], [59, 78, "ORG"], [42, 50, "PERSON"], [166, 172, "DATE"], [0, 6, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5442, "data": "Gary Payton II and his more famous father pose an interesting question to devotees of basketball defense: Is that what the D in DNA stands for?", "label": [[0, 14, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5448, "data": "He got seven of his 33 steals, as well as 11 defensive rebounds, on Feb. 13 against the Ignite elite team.", "label": [[20, 22, "CARDINAL"], [42, 44, "CARDINAL"], [73, 75, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5466, "data": "The award came in the midst of Payton’s nine consecutive All-Defense first-team selections.", "label": [[31, 37, "PERSON"], [57, 68, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5472, "data": "Believe it or not, that’s when Payton II said he believes his embrace of defense began.", "label": [[31, 40, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5478, "data": "“After that, there were a bunch of players I grew up around, coming to the gym, like [Jason] Kidd, Kevin Garnett and other friends of the family.", "label": [[86, 91, "PERSON"], [93, 97, "PERSON"], [99, 112, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5490, "data": "I think that was him putting that in us,” said Payton II, who has four non-playing siblings.", "label": [[47, 56, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5502, "data": "I do watch film on certain guys, and I try to be as disruptive as I can.” The NBA’s developmental league has been giving out its DPOY since 2002.", "label": [[140, 144, "DATE"], [78, 81, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5508, "data": "He played 61 games in the NBA from 2016 to 2020 with the Bucks, the Lakers and the Wizards, and his goal is to get back.", "label": [[26, 29, "ORG"], [35, 39, "DATE"], [43, 47, "DATE"], [57, 62, "ORG"], [10, 12, "CARDINAL"], [68, 74, "ORG"], [83, 90, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5526, "data": "Still, it’s his results as a rim protector and helper – a 6.6 percentage point difference in opponents’ FG%, the 19.5 DFGA he faces and his 0.168 defensive win shares – that fuel the Jazz’s play overall.", "label": [[113, 117, "CARDINAL"], [140, 145, "CARDINAL"], [58, 61, "CARDINAL"], [183, 187, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5538, "data": "But Turner has been in the red each night for a cumulative minus-38, though the team was outscored by 16 in going 1-2.", "label": [[114, 117, "SCORE"], [102, 104, "CARDINAL"], [4, 10, "PERSON"], [59, 67, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5544, "data": "[ NBA.com/Stats | Players Defense Dash Overall ] And in coach Mike Budenholzer’s schemes the past three games, last year’s DPOY and his mates have outscored teams by 10.1 points, limiting them to 42.1% shooting.", "label": [[62, 78, "PERSON"], [166, 170, "CARDINAL"], [196, 201, "PERCENT"]]}
{"id": 5550, "data": "The Sixers have Simmons, Embiid (when healthy) and Matisse Thybulle.", "label": [[4, 10, "ORG"], [16, 23, "PERSON"], [25, 31, "PERSON"], [51, 67, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5556, "data": "Adebayo gets the nod for logging more games, anchoring Miami’s D full-time, and making a 7-point difference when he’s on the floor vs. off.", "label": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [55, 60, "GPE"], [89, 90, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5562, "data": "The views on this page do not necessarily reflect the views of the NBA, its clubs or Turner Broadcasting.", "label": [[85, 104, "ORG"], [67, 70, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5568, "data": "It is Embiid’s highest scoring average against any team he’s faced more than once and his highest field goal percentage against any team he’s faced this season.", "label": [[148, 159, "DATE"], [6, 12, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5574, "data": "Sunday night was tied for the fifth-lowest scoring game the Sixers have had all season.", "label": [[0, 12, "TIME"], [30, 35, "ORDINAL"], [76, 86, "DATE"], [60, 66, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5580, "data": "• With Daniel Theis being traded and Tristan Thompson out tonight due to health and safety protocols, the tall task of locking up Embiid will fall on Robert Williams III .", "label": [[7, 19, "PERSON"], [37, 53, "PERSON"], [150, 169, "PERSON"], [130, 136, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5586, "data": "Tuesday’s game against Philadelphia is the fifth game of a seven-game homestand for the Celtics, who are 15-9 at home this season compared to 10-16 on the road.", "label": [[105, 109, "SCORE"], [142, 147, "SCORE"], [43, 48, "ORDINAL"], [0, 7, "DATE"], [23, 35, "GPE"], [59, 64, "CARDINAL"], [88, 95, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5592, "data": "ET, TNT • The Bucks won the first meeting of the season with the Warriors, 138-99 on Christmas Day , behind Khris Middleton’s 31 points in 26 minutes.", "label": [[14, 19, "ORG"], [126, 128, "CARDINAL"], [139, 149, "TIME"], [75, 81, "SCORE"], [65, 73, "ORG"], [85, 98, "DATE"], [108, 123, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5598, "data": "• During the Bucks’ win on Christmas Day, they shot 20-36 (55.6%) from 3-point range as a team.", "label": [[59, 64, "PERCENT"], [52, 57, "SCORE"], [13, 18, "ORG"], [27, 40, "DATE"], [71, 78, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5600, "data": "There have been 17 games across the league this season in which a team has made at least 20 3-pointers while shooting 55% or better from beyond the arc — the Bucks lead the league with four such games; the Warriors have one.", "label": [[89, 91, "CARDINAL"], [92, 102, "PRODUCT"], [118, 121, "PERCENT"], [206, 214, "ORG"], [158, 163, "ORG"], [185, 189, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5604, "data": "They will face a Warriors team ranked ninth in defensive efficiency (110.3) and seventh in opponent effective field goal percentage (52.7%).", "label": [[17, 25, "ORG"], [69, 74, "CARDINAL"], [133, 138, "PERCENT"], [80, 87, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5610, "data": "• This is the fifth game of a six-game road trip for the Bucks, which began on March 29 with a loss to the Clippers, followed by three straight wins against the Lakers, Kings and Blazers.", "label": [[14, 19, "ORDINAL"], [57, 62, "ORG"], [79, 87, "DATE"], [107, 115, "ORG"], [161, 167, "ORG"], [169, 174, "ORG"], [179, 186, "ORG"], [30, 33, "CARDINAL"], [129, 134, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5616, "data": "Denver’s Nikola Jokic (20 in 25 games) is the only player with more road double-doubles than Giannis.", "label": [[0, 6, "GPE"], [9, 21, "PERSON"], [23, 25, "CARDINAL"], [29, 31, "CARDINAL"], [93, 100, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5628, "data": "He’s still underpriced at $5.8K.", "label": [[27, 31, "MONEY"]]}
{"id": 5634, "data": "The big man has been highly productive for Portland this season with Nurkic on the shelf for most of the campaign.", "label": [[43, 51, "GPE"], [52, 63, "DATE"], [69, 75, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5640, "data": "In the three games he went for 30 FD points, Diallo racked up at least seven boards and multiple combined blocks/steals.", "label": [[31, 33, "CARDINAL"], [45, 51, "PERSON"], [71, 76, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5646, "data": "Last night, he went for 16/6/4 with three blocks and four steals, and with Kyle Lowry already ruled out and Fred VanVleet questionable, Flynn could see heavy usage again.", "label": [[75, 85, "PERSON"], [108, 121, "PERSON"], [0, 10, "DATE"], [36, 41, "CARDINAL"], [53, 57, "CARDINAL"], [24, 30, "CARDINAL"], [136, 141, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5652, "data": "Grayson Allen (MEM): $4,700 at MIA Allen provided his second-highest FD point total of the season Sunday against Philly, and he’ll look to keep the momentum going tonight in a friendly matchup with Miami.", "label": [[21, 27, "MONEY"], [0, 13, "PERSON"], [31, 34, "ORG"], [35, 40, "PERSON"], [54, 60, "ORDINAL"], [98, 104, "DATE"], [113, 119, "GPE"], [198, 203, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5658, "data": "If you’re looking to pay down at center, there isn’t a better bang for your buck than Hernangomez.", "label": [[86, 97, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5670, "data": "Hayes is still priced at the bare minimum, and that’s a salary to exploit.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5676, "data": "Yes, that 10-game stretch told us plenty about the Sixers, about Tobias Harris, about Ben Simmons and coach Doc Rivers.", "label": [[10, 12, "CARDINAL"], [51, 57, "ORG"], [65, 78, "PERSON"], [86, 97, "PERSON"], [108, 118, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5682, "data": "“When I got hurt, and was laying on the floor in Washington, honestly, I thought I was done,” Embiid said.", "label": [[94, 100, "PERSON"], [49, 59, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5688, "data": "Meanwhile, the Bucks — who finished with the NBA’s best record the last two seasons — were aggressively seeking to reclaim a familiar spot.", "label": [[15, 20, "ORG"], [45, 48, "ORG"], [63, 83, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5694, "data": "In the estimation of 76ers reserve center Dwight Howard, they played “lights out” given the circumstances.", "label": [[21, 26, "ORG"], [42, 55, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5700, "data": "Then there were those who helped — Howard, Shake Milton, Seth Curry — and had moments when their minutes, roles and importance increased minus Embiid.", "label": [[43, 55, "PERSON"], [35, 41, "PERSON"], [57, 67, "PERSON"], [143, 149, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5706, "data": "These were the most obvious: The schedule cooperates: The Sixers saw only four top-five teams in those 10 games without Embiid, and one of them was the Los Angeles Lakers without LeBron James and Anthony Davis.", "label": [[103, 105, "CARDINAL"], [120, 126, "PERSON"], [148, 170, "ORG"], [179, 191, "PERSON"], [196, 209, "PERSON"], [58, 64, "ORG"], [79, 87, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5712, "data": "Tobias Harris’ play: He averaged 22 ppg, 7.4 rpg and 4.3 apg in a well-rounded March and took over for Embiid as the primary scoring option, making an efficient 52.5% of his shots.", "label": [[33, 35, "CARDINAL"], [41, 44, "CARDINAL"], [53, 56, "CARDINAL"], [161, 166, "PERCENT"], [103, 109, "ORDINAL"], [79, 84, "DATE"], [0, 13, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5718, "data": "At the very least, he’s a far different player than the one who struggled in the 2020 playoffs, and he’ll be looking to avenge that performance, too.", "label": [[81, 85, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5724, "data": "Instead, Simmons leaned on his strengths after returning from his own absence due to health and safety protocols, and provided typically solid defense (opponents scored 101 points or less in six of the 10 games against Philly) along with the rebounding help the Sixers needed without Embiid.", "label": [[9, 16, "PERSON"], [169, 172, "CARDINAL"], [191, 194, "CARDINAL"], [202, 204, "CARDINAL"], [219, 225, "GPE"], [262, 268, "ORG"], [284, 290, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5730, "data": "Curry scored 21 in that blowout and the Sixers played with a noticeable swagger.", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [13, 15, "CARDINAL"], [40, 46, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5736, "data": "Dwight Howard plugging the gap: Quite predictably, Howard saw an uptick in minutes at center and performed as well as could be expected, if not better in some spots.", "label": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [51, 57, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5742, "data": "Once again, here in his twilight, Howard has landed a comfortable role with a team that needs him.", "label": [[34, 40, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5748, "data": "It was a meeting that easily could’ve gone south for the Sixers, yet they showed plenty of spunk by sticking with the Bucks and forcing Milwaukee to pull its two-time MVP emergency cord.", "label": [[167, 170, "PRODUCT"], [118, 123, "ORG"], [57, 63, "ORG"], [136, 145, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5754, "data": "What happens from here for Philly?", "label": [[27, 33, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5760, "data": "That means Embiid will fortify a team that will seek to finish strong while also attempting to reclaim his place in line for the MVP race.", "label": [[11, 17, "ORDINAL"], [129, 132, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5766, "data": "When we trust it and do what is asked of us, we’re a hell of a team.” * * * Shaun Powell has covered the NBA for more than 25 years.", "label": [[105, 108, "ORG"], [123, 131, "DATE"], [76, 88, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5772, "data": "NBA TV will premiere a two-part special, Ready or Not: The 96 NBA Draft, on Sunday, April 11, at 8 p.m.", "label": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [59, 61, "CARDINAL"], [62, 71, "ORG"], [76, 82, "DATE"], [84, 92, "DATE"], [94, 103, "TIME"]]}
{"id": 5778, "data": "Four future Naismith Basketball Hall of Famers were selected in the 1996 NBA Draft, starting with first overall pick Allen Iverson, followed by Ray Allen, Kobe Bryant and Steve Nash.", "label": [[68, 72, "DATE"], [73, 82, "ORG"], [117, 130, "PERSON"], [144, 153, "PERSON"], [155, 166, "PERSON"], [171, 181, "PERSON"], [12, 46, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5784, "data": "Ready or Not — themed after the chart-topping 1996 Fugees song of the same name — features rare pre-Draft footage, candid moments from the green room, plus interviews with more than 30 former NBA players, coaches and executives, including Iverson, Allen, Nash, Jerry West and Rick Pitino.", "label": [[276, 287, "PERSON"], [261, 271, "PERSON"], [248, 253, "PERSON"], [239, 246, "PERSON"], [192, 195, "ORG"], [255, 259, "ORG"], [182, 184, "CARDINAL"], [46, 50, "DATE"], [51, 57, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5790, "data": "The Baylor Bears won their first NCAA tournament championship on Monday, beating Gonzaga, 86-70 , and did it with the help of NBA Academies product Jonathan Tchamwa Tchatchoua.", "label": [[90, 95, "SCORE"], [148, 175, "PERSON"], [33, 37, "ORG"], [65, 71, "DATE"], [126, 129, "ORG"], [81, 88, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5796, "data": "Center Oumar Ballo, who averaged 2.5 points and 1.5 rebounds in 6.2 minutes for Gonzaga during the regular season, wasn’t on the Bulldog’s active roster Monday.", "label": [[7, 18, "PERSON"], [33, 36, "CARDINAL"], [48, 51, "CARDINAL"], [64, 75, "TIME"], [153, 159, "DATE"], [80, 87, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5802, "data": "), importance (playoff game or garden-variety night in November?)", "label": [[55, 63, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5808, "data": "Even as a miserable, COVID-19 displaced campaign unfolds for the Toronto Raptors in Tampa, they just … keep … hanging … on.", "label": [[65, 80, "ORG"], [84, 89, "GPE"], [21, 29, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5820, "data": "GAME SITUATION: The Wizards won each of the first three quarters, entering the fourth with an 11-point margin and Russell Westbrook well on his way to yet another triple-double (final line: 23 points, 14 rebounds, 11 assists).", "label": [[190, 192, "CARDINAL"], [201, 203, "CARDINAL"], [214, 216, "CARDINAL"], [20, 27, "ORG"], [44, 49, "ORDINAL"], [50, 55, "CARDINAL"], [79, 85, "ORDINAL"], [94, 96, "CARDINAL"], [114, 131, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5822, "data": "With the Wizards going cold from range — missing 13 straight 3-pointers at one point — the Raptors raced out at the beginning of the quarter, eventually snatching a 91-90 lead and creating a battle the rest of the way.", "label": [[49, 51, "CARDINAL"], [61, 71, "PRODUCT"], [165, 170, "SCORE"], [9, 16, "ORG"], [91, 98, "ORG"], [112, 140, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5826, "data": "Toronto turned it over on a Pascal Siakam charging call, the Wizards’ Raul Neto missed a layup and Trent grabbed the rebound with 4.4 seconds on the clock and room to run.", "label": [[0, 7, "GPE"], [28, 41, "PERSON"], [61, 68, "ORG"], [70, 79, "PERSON"], [130, 133, "CARDINAL"], [99, 104, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5832, "data": "One quick left-to-right crossover opened a lane to the top of the opposite end of the logo, and a hard right-to-left behind-the-back dribble (perhaps aided by a little nudge) cleared the room for a pullup 3-pointer as time expired.", "label": [[205, 214, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5844, "data": "If Toronto somehow salvages a postseason run, this single shot might loom large.", "label": [[3, 10, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5850, "data": "James Harden left in the first quarter with right hamstring tightness and was soon ruled out for the night after playing only 4 minutes, 22 seconds.", "label": [[0, 12, "PERSON"], [126, 135, "TIME"], [137, 147, "TIME"], [21, 38, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5856, "data": "He was originally hurt against Houston last Wednesday, missing the final quarter of a victory against his former team.", "label": [[31, 38, "GPE"], [44, 53, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5862, "data": "“But it’s definitely not set in stone,” Nets coach Steve Nash said after Monday’s game.", "label": [[40, 44, "ORG"], [51, 61, "PERSON"], [73, 79, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5868, "data": "Information from The Associated Press was used in this report.", "label": [[21, 37, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5874, "data": "It’s not known how much longer he’ll be out after missing 29 of Atlanta’s last 31 games.", "label": [[58, 60, "CARDINAL"], [79, 81, "CARDINAL"], [64, 71, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 5880, "data": "Hunter’s return was short-lived.", "label": [[0, 6, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5886, "data": "He ranks third on the team in scoring (16.0 points per game), providing another offensive weapon to go with Trae Young and John Collins.", "label": [[39, 43, "CARDINAL"], [108, 118, "PERSON"], [123, 135, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5892, "data": "North Carolina has turned to former Tar Heels player and assistant coach Hubert Davis to lead the storied men’s basketball program as the successor to Hall of Famer Roy Williams.", "label": [[0, 14, "GPE"], [73, 85, "PERSON"], [36, 45, "ORG"], [151, 168, "ORG"], [169, 177, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5898, "data": "UNC is planning an introductory news conference for Davis on Tuesday.", "label": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [52, 57, "PERSON"], [61, 68, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5904, "data": "I am proud to lead this team, and I can’t wait for all that comes next.” Williams retired last week after 18 seasons at his alma mater in a career that also included 15 years at Kansas and 903 overall victories.", "label": [[73, 81, "PERSON"], [166, 174, "DATE"], [178, 184, "GPE"], [189, 192, "CARDINAL"], [90, 99, "DATE"], [106, 108, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 5910, "data": "It has worked before, with longtime assistant Bill Guthridge taking over after Smith’s 1997 retirement and leading the Tar Heels to two Final Fours, as well as Williams’ return from Kansas in 2003.", "label": [[160, 168, "PERSON"], [182, 188, "GPE"], [192, 196, "DATE"], [79, 84, "PERSON"], [87, 91, "DATE"], [119, 128, "ORG"], [132, 135, "CARDINAL"], [46, 60, "PERSON"], [136, 147, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5916, "data": "His hiring also marks a groundbreaking moment as the first Black coach in the history of the program.", "label": [[53, 58, "ORDINAL"], [59, 64, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5922, "data": "He had also served as head coach of the UNC junior varsity program and oversaw the program’s charitable endeavors.", "label": [[40, 43, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5924, "data": "Davis, the nephew of former UNC player and NBA All-Star Walter Davis, played for Smith from 1988-92 and still holds the program record for career 3-point percentage (.435).", "label": [[0, 5, "PERSON"], [28, 31, "ORG"], [43, 46, "ORG"], [47, 55, "PRODUCT"], [56, 68, "PERSON"], [81, 86, "ORG"], [92, 99, "DATE"], [146, 153, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5928, "data": "Davis went onto become a first-round NBA draft pick by the New York Knicks and spent a dozen seasons in the league.", "label": [[25, 30, "ORDINAL"], [0, 5, "PERSON"], [59, 74, "ORG"], [37, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5940, "data": "MILWAUKEE — Jrue Holiday says it was an easy decision to sign a contract extension in his first season with the Milwaukee Bucks.", "label": [[112, 127, "ORG"], [0, 9, "GPE"], [12, 24, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5946, "data": "“I feel like you can tell when somebody’s like super excited or happy about something, and you could hear it in his voice,” Holiday said Monday, one day after agreeing to terms on a four-year extension that would be worth at least $134 million if he exercises his option for the final season.", "label": [[124, 131, "PERSON"], [137, 143, "DATE"], [231, 243, "MONEY"], [182, 191, "DATE"], [275, 291, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 5958, "data": "There are incentives that could push the total value of Holiday’s deal to nearly $160 million.", "label": [[81, 93, "MONEY"], [56, 63, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 5970, "data": "They made it an easy decision.” The Bucks acquired Holiday from the New Orleans Pelicans in November as part of a four-team trade.", "label": [[36, 41, "ORG"], [92, 100, "DATE"], [114, 118, "CARDINAL"], [51, 58, "PERSON"], [68, 88, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5976, "data": "The Bucks believe the 6-foot-3 Holiday has been worth the price.", "label": [[22, 30, "CARDINAL"], [31, 38, "PERSON"], [0, 9, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 5982, "data": "He was named the Eastern Conference player of the week Monday after averaging 26.8 points, 8.5 assists, 5.8 rebounds and 2.5 steals over his last four games, all on the road.", "label": [[55, 61, "DATE"], [78, 82, "CARDINAL"], [91, 94, "CARDINAL"], [104, 107, "CARDINAL"], [121, 124, "CARDINAL"], [141, 145, "ORDINAL"], [146, 150, "CARDINAL"], [17, 42, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5988, "data": "Holiday received an NBA Cares community assist award in January for his efforts to support people impacted by the pandemic.", "label": [[56, 63, "DATE"], [0, 7, "PERSON"], [20, 52, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 5994, "data": "That figure would reach $120 million in 2023-24 if Middleton exercises an option he has for that season.", "label": [[24, 36, "MONEY"], [40, 47, "DATE"], [51, 60, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6000, "data": "“They built together for so long and they won together for so long that I feel like it kind of came to a point where they were just this well-oiled machine and knew each other and knew how things were going to go,” Holiday said.", "label": [[215, 222, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6006, "data": "The former All-Star guard has been out since Feb. 8 as he recovered from arthroscopic surgery on his left knee.", "label": [[11, 19, "PRODUCT"], [45, 51, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6012, "data": "MINNEAPOLIS – The Minnesota Timberwolves today announced the following injury update on guard Malik Beasley, who missed the last game due to left hamstring soreness: An MRI (Magnetic Resonance Imaging) taken today at Mayo Clinic Square on Beasley revealed a grade 3 left hamstring injury.", "label": [[0, 11, "GPE"], [14, 40, "ORG"], [174, 200, "PRODUCT"], [169, 172, "PRODUCT"], [217, 235, "ORG"], [239, 246, "PERSON"], [264, 265, "CARDINAL"], [94, 107, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6018, "data": "In 37 games (36 starts) this season, Beasley is averaging 19.6 points on 44.0% shooting, 4.4 rebounds and 2.4 assists.", "label": [[3, 5, "CARDINAL"], [13, 15, "CARDINAL"], [24, 35, "DATE"], [37, 44, "PERSON"], [58, 62, "CARDINAL"], [73, 78, "PERCENT"], [89, 92, "CARDINAL"], [106, 109, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6024, "data": "The 6-foot-10 center is one of 11 players in NBA history to average at least 20.0 points, 10.0 rebounds and 3.0 assists.", "label": [[4, 13, "CARDINAL"], [31, 33, "CARDINAL"], [45, 48, "ORG"], [77, 81, "CARDINAL"], [90, 94, "CARDINAL"], [108, 111, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6030, "data": "Dallas Mavericks guard Luka Doncic and Milwaukee Bucks guard Jrue Holiday have been named the NBA Players of the Week for Week 15.", "label": [[122, 129, "DATE"], [90, 117, "PRODUCT"], [23, 34, "PERSON"], [39, 54, "ORG"], [61, 73, "PERSON"], [0, 16, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6036, "data": "29) 25 points (9-17 FG, 4-10 3P), 3 rebounds, 7 assists, 2 steals > Video Box Score Mavericks 113, Celtics 108 (Mar.", "label": [[0, 2, "CARDINAL"], [4, 6, "CARDINAL"], [15, 19, "SCORE"], [24, 28, "SCORE"], [34, 35, "CARDINAL"], [46, 47, "CARDINAL"], [57, 58, "CARDINAL"], [84, 93, "ORG"], [99, 106, "ORG"], [107, 110, "CARDINAL"], [94, 97, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6042, "data": "3) 26 points (12-24 FG), 8 rebounds, 6 assists, 1 steal, 1 block > Video Box Score Clippers 129, Bucks 105  (Mar.", "label": [[97, 102, "ORG"], [83, 91, "ORG"], [92, 95, "CARDINAL"], [103, 106, "CARDINAL"], [3, 5, "CARDINAL"], [14, 19, "SCORE"], [25, 26, "CARDINAL"], [37, 38, "CARDINAL"], [48, 49, "CARDINAL"], [57, 58, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6048, "data": "2) 22 points (9-14 FG), 4 rebounds, 10 assists, 2 steals > Video Box Score Bucks 129, Kings 128  (Apr.", "label": [[3, 5, "CARDINAL"], [14, 18, "SCORE"], [92, 95, "CARDINAL"], [81, 84, "CARDINAL"], [75, 80, "ORG"], [86, 91, "ORG"], [24, 25, "CARDINAL"], [36, 38, "CARDINAL"], [48, 49, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6054, "data": "ET, NBA League Pass The Jazz enter Week 16 riding a nine-game win streak.", "label": [[4, 7, "ORG"], [40, 42, "CARDINAL"], [20, 28, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6060, "data": "During their current streak (which dates back to March 19), Donovan Mitchell has averaged 28.1 points on 53.1%-51.6%-95.3% shooting splits, while Rudy Gobert has averaged 15.7 ppg on 68.9% shooting, 12.0 rpg and 3.3 bpg.", "label": [[49, 57, "DATE"], [90, 94, "CARDINAL"], [105, 122, "PERCENT"], [171, 175, "CARDINAL"], [183, 188, "PERCENT"], [199, 203, "CARDINAL"], [212, 215, "CARDINAL"], [146, 157, "PERSON"], [60, 76, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6066, "data": "Dallas is also looking for its first win over Utah as the Jazz swept a two-game series in late January.", "label": [[0, 6, "GPE"], [46, 50, "GPE"], [54, 62, "ORG"], [31, 36, "ORDINAL"], [71, 74, "CARDINAL"], [90, 102, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6072, "data": "With the race to the playoffs in full swing, there is plenty to keep an eye on, from the battles among the top seeds for home-court advantage, to the race to get in the Play-In Tournament among the No.7-10 seeds in each conference.", "label": [[198, 205, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6078, "data": "Tuesday is the second of three regular season games between these teams with a potential playoff matchup looming.", "label": [[0, 7, "DATE"], [15, 21, "ORDINAL"], [25, 30, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6084, "data": "Is Dame ready for a breakout game against LA?", "label": [[42, 44, "GPE"], [3, 7, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6096, "data": "If the season ended today, they would meet in the Play-In Tournament, but the East standings so crowded (currently there are only three games separating No.4 and No.9) there is an opportunity to climb the standings and lock up a playoff spot.", "label": [[20, 25, "DATE"], [74, 82, "ORG"], [130, 135, "CARDINAL"], [153, 157, "ORDINAL"], [162, 166, "ORDINAL"], [50, 68, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6102, "data": "ET, NBA League Pass The Bucks held Giannis Antetokounmpo (left knee soreness) out of the lineup against Sacramento on Saturday, but the Bucks still got the win thanks to a season-high 33 points (as well as 11 assists) from Jrue Holiday, who signed a four-year contract extension one day later.", "label": [[0, 2, "ORG"], [4, 19, "ORG"], [20, 29, "ORG"], [35, 56, "PERSON"], [104, 114, "PERSON"], [118, 126, "DATE"], [132, 141, "ORG"], [184, 186, "CARDINAL"], [206, 208, "CARDINAL"], [223, 235, "PERSON"], [250, 259, "DATE"], [279, 286, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6108, "data": "Giannis finished with 31 points on 14-21 shooting and nine rebounds, while Doncic recorded one of nine triple-doubles this season with 28 points, 13 assists and 10 rebounds in the loss.", "label": [[0, 7, "PERSON"], [22, 24, "CARDINAL"], [35, 40, "SCORE"], [54, 58, "CARDINAL"], [75, 81, "PERSON"], [118, 129, "DATE"], [135, 137, "CARDINAL"], [146, 148, "CARDINAL"], [161, 163, "CARDINAL"], [91, 102, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6114, "data": "ET, NBA League Pass After missing 10 games due to a bone bruise in his left knee, Joel Embiid return to the Sixers on Saturday and finished with 24 points, eight rebounds and three blocks in 29 minutes in a win over Minnesota.", "label": [[34, 36, "CARDINAL"], [0, 2, "ORG"], [4, 19, "ORG"], [82, 93, "PERSON"], [104, 114, "ORG"], [118, 126, "DATE"], [145, 147, "CARDINAL"], [156, 161, "CARDINAL"], [175, 180, "CARDINAL"], [191, 201, "TIME"], [216, 225, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 6116, "data": "Tobias Harris continued his strong play as he led the Sixers with 32 points on 13-17 (76.5%) shooting from the field, 66.7% (2-3) from 3-point range and 100% (4-4) from the free throw line.", "label": [[0, 13, "PERSON"], [50, 60, "ORG"], [66, 68, "CARDINAL"], [79, 84, "SCORE"], [86, 91, "PERCENT"], [118, 123, "PERCENT"], [125, 128, "SCORE"], [135, 142, "PRODUCT"], [153, 157, "PERCENT"], [159, 162, "SCORE"]]}
{"id": 6120, "data": "If he could finish the season hitting those marks he would join an exclusive club that includes only eight NBA players.", "label": [[107, 110, "ORG"], [101, 106, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6126, "data": "Williamson is on pace to make over 500 field goals this season.", "label": [[0, 10, "ORDINAL"], [35, 38, "CARDINAL"], [51, 62, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6132, "data": "ET, NBA League Pass The Suns enter Week 16 sitting 3 1/2 games back of the top-seeded Jazz in the West.", "label": [[20, 28, "ORG"], [4, 19, "ORG"], [0, 2, "ORG"], [86, 90, "ORG"], [35, 42, "DATE"], [51, 56, "CARDINAL"], [94, 102, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 6138, "data": "On the opposite side of the playoff spectrum are the Washington Wizards, who have dropped three straight games and find themselves on the outside looking in at the East Play-In.", "label": [[49, 71, "ORG"], [160, 168, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 6144, "data": "Beal scored 34 points against Phoenix in their first meeting on Jan. 11 as the Wizards handed the Suns their second-biggest loss of the season (21 points).", "label": [[0, 4, "PERSON"], [12, 14, "CARDINAL"], [64, 71, "DATE"], [75, 86, "ORG"], [94, 102, "ORG"], [109, 115, "ORDINAL"], [132, 142, "DATE"], [144, 146, "CARDINAL"], [30, 37, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 6150, "data": "The incident occurred following the conclusion of the Kings’ 129-128 loss to the Milwaukee Bucks on April 3 at Golden 1 Center.", "label": [[61, 68, "SCORE"], [50, 59, "ORG"], [77, 96, "ORG"], [100, 107, "DATE"], [111, 126, "GPE"]]}
{"id": 6156, "data": "The Heat lost Jae Crowder from last year’s playoff rotation and dealt with injuries and COVID-related absences early in the season.", "label": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [14, 25, "PERSON"], [31, 40, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6162, "data": "And the rest of the Eastern Conference wasn’t exactly taking advantage of the struggles in Boston, Miami and Tampa.", "label": [[91, 97, "GPE"], [99, 104, "GPE"], [109, 114, "GPE"], [16, 38, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6168, "data": "But they made this move a month ago before losing six straight.", "label": [[50, 53, "CARDINAL"], [24, 35, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6174, "data": "The Atlanta Hawks (12-4 since March 1), Charlotte Hornets (seemingly bound for a slide with Gordon Hayward’s foot injury ), and New York Knicks (with a difficult remaining schedule) are all in the mix, but not as proven as the teams that fought for the conference title last year.", "label": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [19, 23, "SCORE"], [30, 37, "DATE"], [40, 57, "ORG"], [92, 106, "PERSON"], [128, 143, "ORG"], [270, 279, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6180, "data": "Plus-Minus Players of the Week Teams of the Week East vs. West Schedule strength through Week 15 Movement in the Rankings Week 16 Team to Watch Previous Power Rankings Stats Key Pace : Possessions per 48 minutes (League Rank)  OffRtg : Points scored per 100 possessions (League Rank)  DefRtg : Points allowed per 100 possessions (League Rank)  NetRtg : Point differential per 100 possessions (League Rank) The league has averaged 99.7 possessions (per team) per 48 minutes and 111.3 points scored per 100 possessions this season.", "label": [[462, 472, "TIME"], [501, 504, "CARDINAL"], [477, 482, "CARDINAL"], [254, 257, "CARDINAL"], [94, 96, "CARDINAL"], [201, 211, "TIME"], [313, 316, "CARDINAL"], [376, 379, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6192, "data": "New York allows the lowest 3-point percentage (33.6%) and the third-fewest points in the paint (42.5), which are two areas where the Nets usually thrive.", "label": [[27, 34, "PRODUCT"], [0, 8, "GPE"], [47, 52, "PERCENT"], [96, 100, "CARDINAL"], [113, 116, "CARDINAL"], [129, 137, "ORG"], [62, 67, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6194, "data": "Brooklyn ranks third in 3-point percentage (39.2%) and ninth in points in the paint (49.2 ppg).", "label": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [15, 20, "ORDINAL"], [24, 31, "PRODUCT"], [44, 49, "PERCENT"], [55, 60, "ORDINAL"], [85, 89, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6198, "data": "The Nets defeated the Knicks 117-112 on March 15 as Kyrie Irving (34) and James Harden (21) combined for 55 points with Kevin Durant sidelined.", "label": [[0, 8, "ORG"], [18, 28, "ORG"], [29, 36, "SCORE"], [120, 132, "PERSON"], [105, 107, "CARDINAL"], [40, 48, "DATE"], [52, 64, "PERSON"], [74, 86, "PERSON"], [88, 90, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6204, "data": "When Durant and Harden are off the court, Irving averages 38.3 points per 100 possessions , which is more than six points higher than when all three are on the court together (32.2 points per 100).", "label": [[5, 11, "PERSON"], [16, 22, "PERSON"], [42, 48, "PERSON"], [58, 62, "CARDINAL"], [74, 77, "CARDINAL"], [111, 114, "CARDINAL"], [143, 148, "CARDINAL"], [176, 180, "CARDINAL"], [192, 195, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6206, "data": "• Jeff Green is one of six Nets to appear in both games against New York and has averaged 15.5 points on 70.6% (12-for-17) shooting from the field and 83.3% (5-for-6) from 3-point range.", "label": [[112, 121, "SCORE"], [105, 110, "PERCENT"], [90, 94, "CARDINAL"], [2, 12, "PERSON"], [27, 31, "ORG"], [64, 72, "GPE"], [151, 156, "PERCENT"], [158, 165, "SCORE"], [172, 179, "PRODUCT"]]}
{"id": 6210, "data": "• In two games against the Nets this season, Julius Randle is averaging 31.5 points, 9.5 rebounds, 5.5 assists and 2.5 steals.", "label": [[5, 8, "CARDINAL"], [23, 31, "ORG"], [32, 43, "DATE"], [45, 58, "PERSON"], [72, 76, "CARDINAL"], [85, 88, "CARDINAL"], [99, 102, "CARDINAL"], [115, 118, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6216, "data": "RJ Barrett ranks third among eligible second-year players in scoring (17.2 ppg) and sixth in rebounding (5.9 rpg).", "label": [[0, 10, "PERSON"], [17, 22, "ORDINAL"], [38, 44, "ORDINAL"], [70, 74, "CARDINAL"], [84, 89, "ORDINAL"], [105, 108, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6222, "data": "The grants will enhance and build upon the important work of these national and local organizations that align with the NBA Foundation’s mission to provide skills training, mentorship, coaching and pipeline development for high school, college-aged, job-ready and mid-career individuals in Black communities across the United States and Canada.", "label": [[315, 332, "GPE"], [337, 343, "GPE"], [116, 134, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6228, "data": "Braven Braven is a national organization that empowers promising college students with the skills, confidence, experiences and networks necessary to transition from college to stable first jobs, which lead to meaningful careers and lives of impact.", "label": [[0, 13, "ORDINAL"], [183, 188, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6234, "data": "In partnership with teachers and schools, City Year AmeriCorps members cultivate learning environments where all students can build on their strengths and thrive while acquiring valuable skills and experiences that prepare them for career success.", "label": [[42, 62, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6240, "data": "NAF NAF is a national organization solving some of the biggest challenges facing education and workforce development by bringing education, business and community leaders together to increase access to opportunities for more than 100,000 high school students that help them reach their full potential.", "label": [[0, 3, "ORG"], [4, 7, "ORG"], [230, 237, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6246, "data": "In December 2020, the NBA Foundation announced exalt , Management Leadership for Tomorrow , Marcus Graham Project , Operation DREAM , TEAM Inc. , The Knowledge House and the Youth Empowerment Project as inaugural grant recipients.", "label": [[3, 16, "DATE"], [18, 36, "ORG"], [134, 138, "PRODUCT"], [116, 131, "PRODUCT"], [55, 89, "PRODUCT"], [92, 113, "PRODUCT"], [170, 199, "ORG"], [146, 165, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6252, "data": "To learn more about the NBA Foundation or apply for a grant, please visit www.nbafoundation.com .", "label": [[20, 38, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6258, "data": "In case you forgot, the NBA seized upon this novelty of last fall and made it a staple.", "label": [[24, 27, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6264, "data": "The winner of that game is officially the seventh place finisher.", "label": [[42, 49, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6270, "data": "The winner plays the loser of the No.7 vs. No.8 game, and the winner of that game claims the eighth and final playoff spot.", "label": [[34, 38, "ORDINAL"], [43, 47, "ORDINAL"], [93, 99, "ORDINAL"], [104, 109, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6276, "data": "For the purpose of this analysis, we’ll take stock of the teams holding at least 12th place at the moment.", "label": [[81, 85, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6282, "data": "And this list is in no particular order: Miami Heat: There’s no question who stands the most to lose by being forced into a Play-In, or worse, missing the playoffs altogether.", "label": [[41, 51, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6288, "data": "If a team with Oladipo, Bam Adebayo, Jimmy Butler, Tyler Herro, Duncan Robinson, Trevor Ariza, Andre Iguodala and Goran Dragic manages to fall short — in the East, no less — it’d be a crime against basketball.", "label": [[15, 22, "PERSON"], [24, 35, "PERSON"], [37, 49, "PERSON"], [51, 62, "PERSON"], [64, 79, "PERSON"], [81, 93, "PERSON"], [95, 109, "PERSON"], [114, 126, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6306, "data": "Dallas Mavericks: The probability of Dallas being in the Play-In tourney is high as it seems unlikely to rise to six or drop out of the picture.", "label": [[0, 16, "ORG"], [37, 43, "GPE"], [113, 116, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6312, "data": "The lack of a great high-volume 3-point shooter hurts a team that leans so heavily on Doncic isolations (he’s fifth in the NBA in total isolation plays).", "label": [[32, 39, "PRODUCT"], [86, 92, "PERSON"], [123, 126, "ORG"], [110, 115, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6318, "data": "Boston Celtics: Do you think the Celtics awaken some mornings in a cold sweat over a nightmare that had them sitting on the fence in the playoff picture, only to rub their eyes and realize it was no nightmare?", "label": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [29, 40, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6324, "data": "The good news is they’re one winning streak away from rising as high as fourth place and away from the desperate pack.", "label": [[72, 78, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6330, "data": "Everyone expects the Celtics to eventually figure it out.", "label": [[17, 28, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6342, "data": "If Dejounte Murray, Derrick White and Lonnie Walker keep improving, the Spurs would be the team nobody wants to see in the Play-In.", "label": [[3, 18, "ORG"], [20, 33, "ORG"], [38, 51, "ORG"], [68, 77, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6348, "data": "And of course, that John Collins is playing for money.", "label": [[20, 32, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6354, "data": "Although the Hawks won eight straight recently, their surge came courtesy of a soft schedule.", "label": [[9, 18, "ORG"], [23, 28, "CARDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6360, "data": "Indiana Pacers: It doesn’t appear that TJ Warren is going to be around to bail them out, which means the Pacers must figure how to reverse a disappointing season on their own.", "label": [[0, 14, "ORG"], [39, 48, "PERSON"], [101, 111, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6366, "data": "This is a team comprised mostly of role players — Justin Holiday, Doug McDermott, TJ McConnell — who do their jobs fairly well.", "label": [[50, 64, "PERSON"], [66, 80, "PERSON"], [82, 94, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6372, "data": "Memphis Grizzlies: They’ve held it together all season while waiting for big man Jaren Jackson Jr. to heal from knee surgery.", "label": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [81, 98, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6378, "data": "If he starts quickly and looks comfortable, the Grizzlies can make a serious run up the standings.", "label": [[44, 57, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6384, "data": "Chicago Bulls: They declared themselves all-in with the midseason trade for Nikola Vucevic … and then went into a tailspin and fell to 10th place.", "label": [[0, 13, "ORG"], [76, 90, "PERSON"], [135, 139, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6390, "data": "He and Vucevic seem compatible on the floor, so now it’s up to the supporting cast to fall in line.", "label": [[7, 14, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6396, "data": "Charlotte Hornets: Until LaMelo Ball grabbed his wrist in pain, and a foot flared for Gordon Hayward, everything was swell … and then it was swollen.", "label": [[0, 17, "ORG"], [86, 100, "ORG"], [25, 36, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6402, "data": "Assuming that Hayward recovers in time and Terry Rozier continues to play solid ball, the fate of the Hornets could fall to youngsters like Devonte’ Graham and Malik Monk.", "label": [[43, 55, "PERSON"], [14, 21, "PERSON"], [98, 109, "ORG"], [140, 155, "PERSON"], [160, 170, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6408, "data": "They’re a lot closer to 10th place than third place.", "label": [[24, 28, "ORDINAL"], [40, 45, "ORDINAL"]]}
{"id": 6414, "data": "That means not only are the Warriors unlikely to fall beyond 10th place, but they’d be very dangerous in a Play-In because of Curry.", "label": [[24, 36, "ORG"], [61, 65, "ORDINAL"], [126, 131, "PERSON"]]}
{"id": 6420, "data": "But right now, by sitting on the edge of playoff contention, the Warriors find themselves in a worst-case scenario — and can only hope their next step won’t be on a banana peel.", "label": [[61, 73, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6426, "data": "That’s not to suggest a team with Pascal Siakam and Fred VanVleet and newcomer Gary Trent Jr. are incapable of doing so … it just would be so unlike them in 2020-21.", "label": [[34, 47, "PERSON"], [52, 65, "PERSON"], [79, 93, "PERSON"], [157, 164, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6432, "data": "The Bradley Beal-Russell Westbrook tandem never gained traction in terms of making a difference in the standings, while Davis Bertans failed pay dividends after cashing in last offseason.", "label": [[17, 34, "PERSON"], [4, 16, "PERSON"], [120, 133, "PERSON"], [172, 186, "DATE"]]}
{"id": 6438, "data": "Harrison Barnes has elevated his game, and when you combine him with De’Aaron Fox and Buddy Hield, it’s not as if the Kings are lacking in scorers.", "label": [[0, 15, "PERSON"], [69, 81, "PERSON"], [86, 97, "PERSON"], [114, 123, "ORG"]]}
{"id": 6444, "data": "Yes, such is the case despite a pair of young foundational forwards in Zion Williamson and Brandon Ingram, who combine for roughly 50 ppg.", "label": [[71, 86, "PERSON"], [91, 105, "PERSON"], [131, 133, "CARDINAL"]]}
